<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="ACE">
    <Package name="Advanced_Fatigue">
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_DisplayName">
            <English>ACE Advanced Fatigue</English>
            <German>ACE Erweiterte Ausdauer</German>
            <Chinese>ACE 進階疲勞</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>ACE 进阶疲劳</Chinesesimp>
            <Japanese>ACE アドバンスド ファティーグ</Japanese>
            <Italian>ACE Fatica Avanzata</Italian>
            <Korean>ACE 고급 피로도</Korean>
            <French>ACE Fatigue avancée</French>
            <Polish>ACE Zaawansowane Zmęczenie</Polish>
            <Russian>ACE Продвинутая усталость</Russian>
            <Portuguese>ACE Fadiga Avançada</Portuguese>
            <Czech>ACE Pokročilá únava</Czech>
            <Turkish>ACE Gelişmiş Yorgunluk</Turkish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_PerformanceFactor">
            <English>Performance Factor</English>
            <German>Leistungsfaktor</German>
            <Japanese>パフォーマンス因数</Japanese>
            <Polish>Współczynnik wydolności</Polish>
            <Korean>성능 요인</Korean>
            <French>Facteur de performance</French>
            <Italian>Fattore Prestazione</Italian>
            <Chinese>體力值</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>体力值</Chinesesimp>
            <Russian>Фактор производительности</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Fator de Performance</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Faktor výkonu</Czech>
            <Turkish>Performans Faktörü</Turkish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_PerformanceFactor_Description">
            <English>Influences the overall performance of all players with no custom factor. Higher means better.</English>
            <German>Beinflusst die Leistungsfähigkeit aller Spieler ohne eigenen Leistungsfaktor. Ein höherer Wert bedeutet bessere Leistung.</German>
            <Japanese>個別の因数を設定されていない、全てのプレイヤーのあらゆるパフォーマンスに影響を与えます。 値が高ければ高いほど、良い効果が得られます。</Japanese>
            <Polish>Wpływa na ogólną wydolność organizmu u wszystkich graczy bez ustawionego niestandardowego współczynnika. Więcej znaczy lepiej.</Polish>
            <Korean>모든 성능이 임의로 설정된 값 없이 영향받습니다. 값이 클수록 더 나은 성능을 발휘합니다</Korean>
            <French>Impacte la performance globale de tous les joueurs n'ayant pas de facteur personnalisé.\nPlus la valeur est élevée, plus le joueur est performant.</French>
            <Italian>Influenza qualsiasi prestazione di tutti i giocatori smuniti di un fattore personalizzato. Maggiore significa migliore.</Italian>
            <Chinese>影響所有玩家的體力表現，值越高代表體力越好</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>影响所有玩家的体力表现，值越高代表体力越好</Chinesesimp>
            <Russian>Влияет на общую производительность игроков, у которых не задано персональное значение.</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Influencia na performance geral de todos os jogadores sem nenhum fator personalizado. Quanto maior, melhor.</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Ovlivňuje celkový výkon všech hráčů bez vlastního faktoru. Vyšší znamená lépe.</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_PerformanceFactor_EdenDescription">
            <English>Influences the overall performance of this unit. Higher means better.</English>
            <German>Beinflusst die Leistungsfähigkeit dieser Einheit. Ein höherer Wert bedeutet bessere Leistung.</German>
            <Japanese>このユニットのあらゆるパフォーマンスに影響を与えます。 値が高ければ高いほど、良い効果が得られます。</Japanese>
            <Polish>Wpływa na ogólną wydolność tej jednostki. Więcej znaczy lepiej.</Polish>
            <Korean>모든 성능이 이 단위로 영향을 받습니다. 값이 클수록 더 나은 성능을 발휘합니다</Korean>
            <French>Impacte la performance globale de cette unité.\nPlus la valeur est élevée, plus l'unité est performante.</French>
            <Italian>Influenza qualsiasi prestazione di questa unità. Maggiore significa migliore.</Italian>
            <Chinese>影響這個單位的體力表現，值越高代表體力越好</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>影响这个单位的体力表现，值越高代表体力越好</Chinesesimp>
            <Russian>Влияет на общую производительность юнита.</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Influencia na performance geral dessa unidade. Quanto maior, melhor.</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Ovlivňuje celkový výkon této jednotky. Vyšší znamená lépe.</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_RecoveryFactor">
            <English>Recovery Factor</English>
            <German>Erholungsfaktor</German>
            <Japanese>回復因数</Japanese>
            <Polish>Współczynnik regeneracji</Polish>
            <Korean>회복 요인</Korean>
            <French>Facteur de récupération</French>
            <Italian>Fattore Recupero</Italian>
            <Chinese>回復值</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>回复值</Chinesesimp>
            <Russian>Фактор восстановления</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Fator de Recuperação</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Faktor zotavení</Czech>
            <Turkish>Kurtarma Faktörü</Turkish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_RecoveryFactor_Description">
            <English>Changes how fast the player recovers when resting. Higher is faster.</English>
            <German>Ändert, wie schnell ein Spieler Ausdauer regeneriert. Ein höherer Wert bedeutet eine schnellere Regeneration.</German>
            <Japanese>プレイヤーが休憩をとる際に、どのくらいの速度でスタミナ回復するかを設定します。 値が高ければ高いほど、早くなります。</Japanese>
            <Polish>Wpływa na czas regeneracji podczas postoju. Więcej znaczy szybciej.</Polish>
            <Korean>얼마나 빨리 회복하는지를 바꿉니다. 값이 클수록 더 나은 성능을 발휘합니다</Korean>
            <French>Modifie la vitesse à laquelle le joueur récupère lorsqu'il se repose.\nPlus la valeur est élevée, plus la récupération est rapide.</French>
            <Italian>Determina in quanto tempo il giocatore recupera quando rilassato. Maggiore significa migliore.</Italian>
            <Chinese>決定玩家休息多久就能回復體力，值越高恢復越快</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>决定玩家休息多久就能回复体力，值越高恢复越快</Chinesesimp>
            <Russian>Изменяет скорость восстановления игрока во время отдыха. Чем выше, тем быстрее.</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Altera o quão rápido um jogador recupera quando descansando. Quanto maior, mais rápido.</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Mění, jak rychle se hráč zotaví, když odpočívá. Vyšší je rychlejší.</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_LoadFactor">
            <English>Load Factor</English>
            <German>Gewichtsfaktor</German>
            <Japanese>重量因数</Japanese>
            <Polish>Współczynnik masy ekwipunku</Polish>
            <Korean>부담 요인</Korean>
            <French>Facteur de charge</French>
            <Italian>Fattore Caricamento</Italian>
            <Chinese>負重量</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>负重量</Chinesesimp>
            <Russian>Фактор нагрузки</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Fator de Carga</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Faktor zatížení</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_LoadFactor_Description">
            <English>Increases or decreases how much weight influences the players performance. Zero means equipment weight has no performance influence.</English>
            <German>Erhöht oder verringert, wie viel Einfluss das Ausrüstungsgewicht auf die Leistung hat. Null heißt, dass es keinen Einfluss hat.</German>
            <Japanese>装備重量がプレイヤーのパフォーマンスにもたらす影響を増減させます。 値をゼロに設定した場合、装備重量はパフォーマンスに影響を与えません。</Japanese>
            <Polish>Zmniejsza lub zwiększa wpływ ciężaru ekwipunku na wydolność gracza. Zero oznacza kompletny brak wpływu na wydolność.</Polish>
            <Korean>플레이어가 무게에 따라 얼마나 영향받는지를 증가시키거나 감소시킵니다. 0의 경우 플레이어가 장비 무게에 영향받지 않습니다.</Korean>
            <French>Augmente ou diminue l'influence du poids sur les performances du joueur.\nUne valeur nulle indique que le poids de l'équipement n'a aucun impact sur les performances.</French>
            <Italian>Incrementa o decrementa quanto il peso influenza le prestazioni dei giocatori. Zero significa che il peso dell'equipaggiamento non ha alcuna influenza nelle prestazioni.</Italian>
            <Chinese>增加或降低玩家所能承受的負重量. 如設定值為0, 代表裝備的重量將不會影響到玩家的體力表現</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>增加或降低玩家所能承受的负重量. 如设定值为0, 代表装备的重量将不会影响到玩家的体力表现</Chinesesimp>
            <Russian>Увеличивает или уменьшает вес, влияющий на производительность игроков. Ноль означает, что вес снаряжения не влияет на производительность</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Aumenta ou diminui o quanto o peso influencia a performance do jogador. Zero significa que o peso não tem impacto algum na performance.</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Zvyšuje nebo snižuje, jak velká váha ovlivňuje výkon hráče. Nulová hodnota znamená, že hmotnost zařízení nemá žádný vliv na výkon.</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_TerrainGradientFactor">
            <English>Terrain Gradient Factor</English>
            <German>Terrainsteigungsfaktor</German>
            <Japanese>地形勾配因数</Japanese>
            <Polish>Współczynnik terenu</Polish>
            <Korean>지형 경사도 요인</Korean>
            <French>Facteur d'inclinaison du terrain</French>
            <Italian>Fattore Pendenza Terreno</Italian>
            <Chinese>地形陡峭影響值</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>地形陡峭影响值</Chinesesimp>
            <Russian>Фактор местности</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Fator de Inclinação do Terreno</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Faktor stoupání terénu</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_TerrainGradientFactor_Description">
            <English>Sets how much steep terrain increases stamina loss. Higher means higher stamina loss.</English>
            <German>Beeinflusst, wie stark Steigungen den Ausdauerverbrauch erhöhen. Ein höherer Wert erhöht den Ausdauerverbrauch.</German>
            <Japanese>急勾配の地形がどれだけスタミナ消費を増大させるかを設定します。 値が高ければ高いほど、スタミナ消費が大きくなります。</Japanese>
            <Polish>Wpływa na to w jakim stopniu stromy teren wpływa na utratę wytrzymałości. Więcej oznacza szybszą utratę wytrzymałości.</Polish>
            <Korean>경사도에 따라 얼마나 피로해지는지를 정합니다.  값이 클수록 더 많은 피로를 유발합니다.</Korean>
            <French>Définit à quel point un terrain escarpé réduit l'endurance du joueur.\nPlus la valeur est élevée, moins le joueur est endurant.</French>
            <Italian>Stabilisce quanto la pendenza del terreno incrementa la perdita della stamina. Maggiore significa più stamina persa.</Italian>
            <Chinese>設定陡峭的地形將會影響多少體力的流失，值越高代表體力流失越快</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>设定陡峭的地形将会影响多少体力的流，失值越高代表体力流失越快</Chinesesimp>
            <Russian>Устанавливает, насколько крутая местность увеличивает потерю выносливости. Чем выше, тем быстрее теряется выносливость.</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Define o quanto que um terreno íngrime aumenta na perda de estamina. Quanto maior, maior a perda de estamina.</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Nastavuje, o kolik strmý terén zvyšuje ztrátu výdrže. Vyšší znamená vyšší ztrátu výdrže.</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_SwayFactor">
            <English>Sway factor</English>
            <German>Verwacklungsfaktor</German>
            <Japanese>手ぶれ因数</Japanese>
            <Chinesesimp>抖动因数</Chinesesimp>
            <Chinese>抖動因素</Chinese>
            <French>Facteur de tremblement</French>
            <Italian>Fattore di oscillazione</Italian>
            <Polish>Czynnik kołysania</Polish>
            <Russian>Фактор колебания прицела</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Fator de Balanço de Mira</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Faktor kývání</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_SwayFactor_Description">
            <English>Influences the amount of weapon sway. Higher means more sway.</English>
            <German>Beeinflusst den Faktor, wie ruhig man eine Waffe halten kann. Ein höherer Wert bedeutet weniger Stabilisierung</German>
            <Japanese>武器を持つ手のぶれ度合いを設定します。 値が高ければ高いほど、手ぶれが強くなります。</Japanese>
            <Chinesesimp>影响手持武器的晃动程度,数值越高,抖动的越厉害.</Chinesesimp>
            <Chinese>影響手持武器晃動程度，數值越高抖動越厲害</Chinese>
            <French>Influe sur l'amplitude du tremblement de l'arme. Une valeur plus élevée signifie plus de tremblement.</French>
            <Italian>Influenza l'ammontare di oscillazione dell'arma. Maggiore significa più oscillazione.</Italian>
            <Polish>Wpływa na poziom kołysania broni. Większa ilość znaczy większe kołysanie.</Polish>
            <Russian>Влияет на колебания прицела оружия. Чем выше - тем больше.</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Influencia a quantidade de balanço da mira da arma. Quanto maior, mais balanço.</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Ovlivňuje množství kývání zbraní. Vyšší znamená více kývání.</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_Enabled">
            <English>Enabled</English>
            <German>Aktiv</German>
            <Japanese>アドバンスド ファティーグを有効化する</Japanese>
            <Polish>Włączone</Polish>
            <Korean>활성화</Korean>
            <French>Activé</French>
            <Italian>Abilitato</Italian>
            <Chinese>啟用</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>启用</Chinesesimp>
            <Russian>Включена</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Ativado</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Povoleno</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_Enabled_Description">
            <English>Enables/disables Advanced Fatigue.</English>
            <German>Aktiviert/deaktiviert Advanced Fatigue.</German>
            <Japanese>アドバンスド ファティーグを有効化します。</Japanese>
            <Polish>Włącza/wyłącza zaawansowaną wytrzymałość</Polish>
            <Korean>고급 피로도 활성화/비활성화</Korean>
            <French>Active/Désactive la fatigue avancée.</French>
            <Italian>Abilita/disabilita la Fatica Avanzata.</Italian>
            <Chinese>啟用/關閉進階體力.</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>启用/关闭进阶体力.</Chinesesimp>
            <Russian>Включает / Отключает Продвинутую усталость</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Ativa/Desativa Fadiga Avançada.</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Aktivuje / deaktivuje Pokročilou únavu.</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_EnableStaminaBar">
            <English>Show stamina bar</English>
            <German>Zeige Ausdauerleiste</German>
            <Japanese>スタミナバーを表示</Japanese>
            <Polish>Pokaż pasek wytrzymałości</Polish>
            <Korean>피로도 막대</Korean>
            <French>Afficher la barre d'endurance</French>
            <Italian>Mostra barra stamina</Italian>
            <Chinese>顯示體力條</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>显示体力条</Chinesesimp>
            <Russian>Показать шкалу усталости</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Exibir barra de estamina</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Zobrazit lištu výdrže</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_EnableStaminaBar_Description">
            <English>Shows the stamina bar.</English>
            <German>Zeigt die Ausdauerleiste an.</German>
            <Japanese>スタミナバーを表示します。</Japanese>
            <Polish>Pokazuje pasek wytrzymałości.</Polish>
            <Korean>피로도 막대를 보여줍니다.</Korean>
            <French>Affiche la barre d'endurance.</French>
            <Italian>Mostra la barra della stamina.</Italian>
            <Chinese>顯示體力條</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>显示体力条</Chinesesimp>
            <Russian>Показывает шкалу усталости.</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Exibe a barra de estamina.</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Zobrazuje lištu výdrže</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_FadeStaminaBar">
            <English>Fade Stamina bar automatically</English>
            <Russian>Скрыть шкалу усталости автоматически</Russian>
            <German>Blende Ausdauerleiste automatisch aus</German>
            <Chinese>體力條自動淡去</Chinese>
            <Italian>Dissolvenza automatica della barra della stamina</Italian>
            <Czech>Automaticky schovat lištu výdrže</Czech>
            <French>Fondu automatique de la barre d'endurance</French>
            <Japanese>自動的にスタミナバーを非表示</Japanese>
            <Polish>Chowaj pasek wytrzymałości automatycznie</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Barra de stamina some automaticamente</Portuguese>
            <Turkish>Dayanıklılık çubuğunu otomatik olarak soldur</Turkish>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_FadeStaminaBar_Description">
            <English>Adjusts transparency of the bar based on stamina status.</English>
            <Russian>Регулирует прозрачность шкалы в зависимости от статуса выносливости.</Russian>
            <German>Passt die Transparenz der Ausdauerleiste abhängig vom Ausdauerstatus an.</German>
            <Chinese>依照目前的體力程度調整體力條之透明度</Chinese>
            <Italian>Regola la trasparenza della barra in base allo stato di affaticamento.</Italian>
            <Czech>Upravuje průhlednost lišty v závislosti na současném stavu výdrže</Czech>
            <French>Règle la transparence de la barre en fonction de l'état d'endurance.</French>
            <Japanese>スタミナの状態に応じて、自動的にバーの透明度を調整します。</Japanese>
            <Polish>Dostosowuje przezroczystość paska na podstawie stanu wytrzymałości.</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Ajusta a transparência da barra baseado no status da stamina</Portuguese>
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>
