<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="ACE">
    <Package name="Advanced_Fatigue">
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_DisplayName">
            <English>ACE Advanced Fatigue</English>
            <Czech>ACE Pokročilá únava</Czech>
            <French>ACE Fatigue avancée</French>
            <Spanish>ACE Fatiga Avanzada</Spanish>
            <Italian>ACE Fatica Avanzata</Italian>
            <Polish>ACE Zaawansowane Zmęczenie</Polish>
            <Portuguese>ACE Fadiga Avançada</Portuguese>
            <Russian>ACE Продвинутая усталость</Russian>
            <German>ACE Erweiterte Ausdauer</German>
            <Korean>ACE 고급 피로도</Korean>
            <Japanese>ACE 高度な疲労</Japanese>
            <Chinese>ACE 進階疲勞</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>ACE 进阶体力</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>ACE Gelişmiş Yorgunluk</Turkish>
            <Ukrainian>ACE Розширена втома</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_EnableStaminaBar">
            <English>Show stamina bar</English>
            <Czech>Zobrazit lištu výdrže</Czech>
            <French>Afficher la barre d'endurance</French>
            <Spanish>Mostrar barra de cansancio</Spanish>
            <Italian>Mostra barra stamina</Italian>
            <Polish>Pokaż pasek wytrzymałości</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Exibir barra de estamina</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Показать шкалу усталости</Russian>
            <German>Zeige Ausdauerleiste</German>
            <Korean>피로도 막대</Korean>
            <Japanese>スタミナバーを表示</Japanese>
            <Chinese>顯示體力條</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>显示体力条</Chinesesimp>
            <Ukrainian>Показати шкалу втоми</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_EnableStaminaBar_Description">
            <English>Shows the stamina bar.</English>
            <Czech>Zobrazuje lištu výdrže</Czech>
            <French>Affiche la barre d'endurance.</French>
            <Spanish>Muestra la barra de cansancio</Spanish>
            <Italian>Mostra la barra della stamina.</Italian>
            <Polish>Pokazuje pasek wytrzymałości.</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Exibe a barra de estamina.</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Показывает шкалу усталости.</Russian>
            <German>Zeigt die Ausdauerleiste an.</German>
            <Korean>피로도 막대를 보여줍니다.</Korean>
            <Japanese>スタミナバーを表示します。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>顯示體力條</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>显示体力条</Chinesesimp>
            <Ukrainian>Показує шкалу втоми.</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_Enabled">
            <English>Enabled</English>
            <Czech>Povoleno</Czech>
            <French>Activé</French>
            <Spanish>Activada</Spanish>
            <Italian>Abilitata</Italian>
            <Polish>Włączone</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Ativado</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Включена</Russian>
            <German>Aktiv</German>
            <Korean>활성화</Korean>
            <Japanese>有効化</Japanese>
            <Chinese>啟用</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>启用</Chinesesimp>
            <Ukrainian>Увімкнено</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_Enabled_Description">
            <English>Enables/disables Advanced Fatigue.</English>
            <Czech>Aktivuje / deaktivuje Pokročilou únavu.</Czech>
            <French>Active/Désactive la fatigue avancée.</French>
            <Spanish>Activa/desactiva la fatiga avanzada</Spanish>
            <Italian>Abilita/Disabilita la Fatica Avanzata.</Italian>
            <Polish>Włącza/wyłącza zaawansowaną wytrzymałość</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Ativa/Desativa Fadiga Avançada.</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Включает/отключает Продвинутую усталость</Russian>
            <German>Aktiviert/deaktiviert Advanced Fatigue.</German>
            <Korean>고급 피로도 활성화/비활성화</Korean>
            <Japanese>高度な疲労を有効/無効化します。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>啟用/關閉進階體力.</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>启用/关闭进阶体力。</Chinesesimp>
            <Ukrainian>Вмикає/вимикає Розширену втому</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_FadeStaminaBar">
            <English>Fade Stamina bar automatically</English>
            <Czech>Automaticky schovat lištu výdrže</Czech>
            <French>Fondu automatique de la barre d'endurance</French>
            <Spanish>Desvanecer la barra de cansancio</Spanish>
            <Italian>Nascondi in automatico la barra della stamina</Italian>
            <Polish>Chowaj pasek wytrzymałości automatycznie</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Barra de stamina some automaticamente</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Скрыть шкалу усталости автоматически</Russian>
            <German>Blende Ausdauerleiste automatisch aus</German>
            <Korean>자동으로 피로도 막대 숨기기</Korean>
            <Japanese>自動的にスタミナバーを非表示</Japanese>
            <Chinese>體力條自動淡去</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>自动淡化体力条</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Dayanıklılık çubuğunu otomatik olarak soldur</Turkish>
            <Ukrainian>Приховати шкалу втоми автоматично</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_FadeStaminaBar_Description">
            <English>Adjusts transparency of the bar based on stamina status.</English>
            <Czech>Upravuje průhlednost lišty v závislosti na současném stavu výdrže</Czech>
            <French>Règle la transparence de la barre en fonction de l'état d'endurance.</French>
            <Spanish>Ajusta la ocultación progresiva de la barra de cansancio</Spanish>
            <Italian>Regola la trasparenza della barra in base allo stato di affaticamento.</Italian>
            <Polish>Dostosowuje przezroczystość paska na podstawie stanu wytrzymałości.</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Ajusta a transparência da barra baseado no status da stamina</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Регулирует прозрачность шкалы в зависимости от статуса выносливости.</Russian>
            <German>Passt die Transparenz der Ausdauerleiste abhängig vom Ausdauerstatus an.</German>
            <Korean>피로도에 따라 피로도 막대의 투명도를 조절합니다.</Korean>
            <Japanese>スタミナの状態に応じて、自動的にバーの透明度を調整します。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>依照目前的體力程度調整體力條之透明度</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>根据体力状况调整体力条的透明度</Chinesesimp>
            <Ukrainian>Регулює прозорість шкали залежно від статусу витривалості.</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_LoadFactor">
            <English>Load Factor</English>
            <Czech>Faktor zatížení</Czech>
            <French>Facteur de charge</French>
            <Spanish>Factor de carga</Spanish>
            <Italian>Fattore Carico</Italian>
            <Polish>Współczynnik masy ekwipunku</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Fator de Carga</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Фактор нагрузки</Russian>
            <German>Gewichtsfaktor</German>
            <Korean>부담 요인</Korean>
            <Japanese>重量因数</Japanese>
            <Chinese>負重量</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>重量系数</Chinesesimp>
            <Ukrainian>Фактор навантаження</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_LoadFactor_Description">
            <English>Increases or decreases how much weight influences the players performance. Zero means equipment weight has no performance influence.</English>
            <Czech>Zvyšuje nebo snižuje, jak velká váha ovlivňuje výkon hráče. Nulová hodnota znamená, že hmotnost zařízení nemá žádný vliv na výkon.</Czech>
            <French>Augmente ou diminue l'influence du poids sur les performances du joueur.\nUne valeur nulle indique que le poids de l'équipement n'a aucun impact sur les performances.</French>
            <Spanish>Aumenta o disminuye cuanto influye el peso en el rendimiento del jugador. Cero significa que el peso no influye en el rendimiento</Spanish>
            <Italian>Determina quanto il peso trasportato influenza le prestazioni dei giocatori. Zero significa che il peso dell'equipaggiamento non influisce sulle prestazioni.</Italian>
            <Polish>Zmniejsza lub zwiększa wpływ ciężaru ekwipunku na wydolność gracza. Zero oznacza kompletny brak wpływu na wydolność.</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Aumenta ou diminui o quanto o peso influencia a performance do jogador. Zero significa que o peso não tem impacto algum na performance.</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Увеличивает или уменьшает вес, влияющий на производительность игроков. Ноль означает, что вес снаряжения не влияет на производительность</Russian>
            <German>Erhöht oder verringert, wie viel Einfluss das Ausrüstungsgewicht auf die Leistung hat. Null heißt, dass es keinen Einfluss hat.</German>
            <Korean>플레이어가 무게에 따라 얼마나 영향받는지를 증가시키거나 감소시킵니다. 0의 경우 플레이어가 장비 무게에 영향받지 않습니다.</Korean>
            <Japanese>装備重量がプレイヤーのパフォーマンスにもたらす影響を増減させます。 値をゼロに設定した場合、装備重量はパフォーマンスに影響を与えません。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>增加或降低玩家所能承受的負重量. 如設定值為0, 代表裝備的重量將不會影響到玩家的體力表現</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>增加或降低玩家所能承受的负重量。如设定值为0，代表装备的重量将不会影响到玩家的体力表现</Chinesesimp>
            <Ukrainian>Збільшує або зменшує вагу, що впливає на продуктивність гравців. Нуль означає, що вага спорядження не впливає на продуктивність</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_PerformanceFactor">
            <English>Performance Factor</English>
            <Czech>Faktor výkonu</Czech>
            <French>Facteur de performance</French>
            <Spanish>Factor de rendimiento</Spanish>
            <Italian>Fattore Prestazione</Italian>
            <Polish>Współczynnik wydolności</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Fator de Performance</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Фактор производительности</Russian>
            <German>Leistungsfaktor</German>
            <Korean>성능 요인</Korean>
            <Japanese>パフォーマンス因数</Japanese>
            <Chinese>體力值</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>体力值</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Performans Faktörü</Turkish>
            <Ukrainian>Фактор продуктивності</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_PerformanceFactor_Description">
            <English>Influences the overall performance of all players with no custom factor. Higher means better.</English>
            <Czech>Ovlivňuje celkový výkon všech hráčů bez vlastního faktoru. Vyšší znamená lépe.</Czech>
            <French>Impacte la performance globale de tous les joueurs n'ayant pas de facteur personnalisé.\nPlus la valeur est élevée, plus le joueur est performant.</French>
            <Spanish>Afecta al rendimiento general de todos los jugadores sin opciones personalizadas. Más alto significa mejor</Spanish>
            <Italian>Influenza la prestazione generale di tutti i giocatori smuniti di un fattore personalizzato. Maggiore significa migliore.</Italian>
            <Polish>Wpływa na ogólną wydolność organizmu u wszystkich graczy bez ustawionego niestandardowego współczynnika. Więcej znaczy lepiej.</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Influencia na performance geral de todos os jogadores sem nenhum fator personalizado. Quanto maior, melhor.</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Влияет на общую производительность игроков, у которых не задано персональное значение. Чем выше, тем лучше.</Russian>
            <German>Beinflusst die Leistungsfähigkeit aller Spieler ohne eigenen Leistungsfaktor. Ein höherer Wert bedeutet bessere Leistung.</German>
            <Korean>모든 성능이 임의로 설정된 값 없이 영향받습니다. 값이 클수록 더 나은 성능을 발휘합니다</Korean>
            <Japanese>個別の因数を設定されていない、全てのプレイヤーのあらゆるパフォーマンスに影響を与えます。 値が高ければ高いほど、良い効果が得られます。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>影響所有玩家的體力表現，值越高代表體力越好</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>影响所有玩家的体力表现，值越高代表体力越好</Chinesesimp>
            <Ukrainian>Впливає на загальну продуктивність гравців, у яких не задано персональне значення. Що вище, то краще.</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_PerformanceFactor_EdenDescription">
            <English>Influences the overall performance of this unit. Higher means better.</English>
            <Czech>Ovlivňuje celkový výkon této jednotky. Vyšší znamená lépe.</Czech>
            <French>Impacte la performance globale de cette unité.\nPlus la valeur est élevée, plus l'unité est performante.</French>
            <Spanish>Afecta al rendimiento de esta unidad. Más alto significa mejor</Spanish>
            <Italian>Influenza la prestazione personalizzata di questa unità. Maggiore significa migliore.</Italian>
            <Polish>Wpływa na ogólną wydolność tej jednostki. Więcej znaczy lepiej.</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Influencia na performance geral dessa unidade. Quanto maior, melhor.</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Влияет на общую производительность юнита.Чем выше, тем лучше.</Russian>
            <German>Beinflusst die Leistungsfähigkeit dieser Einheit. Ein höherer Wert bedeutet bessere Leistung.</German>
            <Korean>모든 성능이 이 단위로 영향을 받습니다. 값이 클수록 더 나은 성능을 발휘합니다</Korean>
            <Japanese>このユニットのあらゆるパフォーマンスに影響を与えます。 値が高ければ高いほど、良い効果が得られます。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>影響這個單位的體力表現，值越高代表體力越好</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>影响这个单位的体力表现，值越高代表体力越好</Chinesesimp>
            <Ukrainian>Впливає на загальну продуктивність юніта, що вища, то краще.</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_RecoveryFactor">
            <English>Recovery Factor</English>
            <Czech>Faktor zotavení</Czech>
            <French>Facteur de récupération</French>
            <Spanish>Factor de recuperación</Spanish>
            <Italian>Fattore Recupero</Italian>
            <Polish>Współczynnik regeneracji</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Fator de Recuperação</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Фактор восстановления</Russian>
            <German>Erholungsfaktor</German>
            <Korean>회복 요인</Korean>
            <Japanese>回復因数</Japanese>
            <Chinese>回復值</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>恢复系数</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Kurtarma Faktörü</Turkish>
            <Ukrainian>Фактор відновлення</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_RecoveryFactor_Description">
            <English>Changes how fast the player recovers when resting. Higher is faster.</English>
            <Czech>Mění, jak rychle se hráč zotaví, když odpočívá. Vyšší je rychlejší.</Czech>
            <French>Modifie la vitesse à laquelle le joueur récupère lorsqu'il se repose.\nPlus la valeur est élevée, plus la récupération est rapide.</French>
            <Spanish>Modifica cómo de rápido se recupera el jugador cuando descansa. Más alto significa mejor</Spanish>
            <Italian>Determina quanto velocemente il giocatore recupera le energie quando si ferma. Maggiore significa migliore.</Italian>
            <Polish>Wpływa na czas regeneracji podczas postoju. Więcej znaczy szybciej.</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Altera o quão rápido um jogador recupera quando descansando. Quanto maior, mais rápido.</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Изменяет скорость восстановления игрока во время отдыха. Чем выше, тем быстрее.</Russian>
            <German>Ändert, wie schnell ein Spieler Ausdauer regeneriert. Ein höherer Wert bedeutet eine schnellere Regeneration.</German>
            <Korean>얼마나 빨리 회복하는지를 바꿉니다. 값이 클수록 더 나은 성능을 발휘합니다</Korean>
            <Japanese>プレイヤーが休憩をとる際に、どのくらいの速度でスタミナ回復するかを設定します。 値が高ければ高いほど、早くなります。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>決定玩家休息多久就能回復體力，值越高恢復越快</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>决定玩家休息多久就能恢复体力，值越高恢复越快</Chinesesimp>
            <Ukrainian>Змінює швидкість відновлення гравця під час відпочинку. Що вища, то швидше.</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_TerrainGradientFactor">
            <English>Terrain Gradient Factor</English>
            <Czech>Faktor stoupání terénu</Czech>
            <French>Facteur d'inclinaison du terrain</French>
            <Spanish>Factor de inclinación del terreno</Spanish>
            <Italian>Fattore Pendenza Terreno</Italian>
            <Polish>Współczynnik terenu</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Fator de Inclinação do Terreno</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Фактор местности</Russian>
            <German>Terrainsteigungsfaktor</German>
            <Korean>지형 경사도 요인</Korean>
            <Japanese>地形勾配因数</Japanese>
            <Chinese>地形陡峭影響值</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>地形陡峭系数</Chinesesimp>
            <Ukrainian>Фактор місцевості</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Fatigue_TerrainGradientFactor_Description">
            <English>Sets how much steep terrain increases stamina loss. Higher means higher stamina loss.</English>
            <Czech>Nastavuje, o kolik strmý terén zvyšuje ztrátu výdrže. Vyšší znamená vyšší ztrátu výdrže.</Czech>
            <French>Définit à quel point un terrain escarpé réduit l'endurance du joueur.\nPlus la valeur est élevée, moins le joueur est endurant.</French>
            <Spanish>Modifica cuanto afecta la inclinación al cansansio. Más alto significa más cansancio</Spanish>
            <Italian>Determina quanto la pendenza del terreno incrementa la perdita della stamina. Maggiore significa più stamina persa.</Italian>
            <Polish>Wpływa na to w jakim stopniu stromy teren wpływa na utratę wytrzymałości. Więcej oznacza szybszą utratę wytrzymałości.</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Define o quanto que um terreno íngrime aumenta na perda de estamina. Quanto maior, maior a perda de estamina.</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Устанавливает, насколько крутая местность увеличивает потерю выносливости. Чем выше, тем быстрее теряется выносливость.</Russian>
            <German>Beeinflusst, wie stark Steigungen den Ausdauerverbrauch erhöhen. Ein höherer Wert erhöht den Ausdauerverbrauch.</German>
            <Korean>경사도에 따라 얼마나 피로해지는지를 정합니다.  값이 클수록 더 많은 피로를 유발합니다.</Korean>
            <Japanese>急勾配の地形がどれだけスタミナ消費を増大させるかを設定します。 値が高ければ高いほど、スタミナ消費が大きくなります。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>設定陡峭的地形將會影響多少體力的流失，值越高代表體力流失越快</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>设定陡峭的地形将会影响多少体力的流失速度，值越高代表体力流失越快</Chinesesimp>
            <Ukrainian>Встановлює, наскільки крута місцевість збільшує втрату витривалості. Що вище, то швидше втрачається витривалість.</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>
