<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="ACE">
    <Package name="Advanced_Ballistics">
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_Description">
            <English>This module enables advanced ballistics simulation - meaning the trajectory of projectiles is influenced by variables like air temperature, atmospheric pressure, humidity, gravity, the type of ammunition and the weapon from which it was fired.</English>
            <Czech>Tento modul umožňuje aktivovat pokročilou balistiku, která vypočítává trajektorii kulky a bere do úvahy věci jako je teplota vzduchu, atmosférický tlak, vlhkost vzduchu, gravitaci, typ munice a zbraň, ze které je náboj vystřelen. To vše přispívá k velmi přesné balistice.</Czech>
            <French>Ce module permet une simulation balistique avancée ; c'est à dire que la trajectoire des projectiles est influencée par des facteurs tels que la température de l'air, la pression atmosphérique, l'humidité, la gravité, le type de munition et l'arme depuis laquelle elle est tirée.</French>
            <Spanish>Este módulo permite la simulación balística avanzada - es decir, la trayectoria de los proyectiles está influenciada por variables como la temperatura del aire, la presión atmosférica, la humedad, la gravedad, el tipo de municiones y el arma desde el que fue disparada.</Spanish>
            <Italian>Questo modulo abilita la simulazione della Balistica Avanzata - essa comporta che la traiettoria dei proiettili è influenzata da variabili come la temperatura dell'aria, pressione atmosferica, umidità, gravità, il tipo di munizione e l'arma da cui è sparata.</Italian>
            <Polish>Moduł ten pozwala aktywować zaawansowaną balistykę biorącą przy obliczeniach trajektorii lotu pocisku pod uwagę takie rzeczy jak temperatura powietrza, ciśnienie atmosferyczne, wilgotność powietrza, siły Coriolisa i Eotvosa, grawitację a także broń z jakiej wykonywany jest strzał oraz rodzaj amunicji. Wszystko to sprowadza się na bardzo dokładne odwzorowanie balistyki.</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Este módulo permite que você ative cálculos de balística avançada, fazendo a trajetória do projétil levar em consideração coisas como temperatura do ar, pressão atmosférica, umidade, a gravidade, a arma no qual o disparo é realizado e o tipo de munição.</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Этот модуль включает симуляцию продвинутой баллистики - при этом на траекторию полета снаряда влияют различные параметры, такие как температура воздуха, атмосферное давление, влажность, гравитация, тип боеприпаса и оружия, из которого произвели выстрел.</Russian>
            <German>Dieses Modul aktiviert die Erweiterte Ballisitk. Die Flugbahn eines Geschosses wird nun von Einflüssen wie z.B Temperatur, Luftdruck, Luftfeuchtigkeit, Schwerkraft, Geschossart sowie der Waffe aus dem es gefeuert wird, beeinflusst.</German>
            <Korean>이 모듈은 고급 탄도학을 적용시킵니다 - 이는 발사체의 궤적이 기온, 대기압, 습도, 중력, 탄환의 종류와 어느 무기에서 발사되는지에 따라 영향을 받습니다.</Korean>
            <Japanese>高度な弾道計算のシミュレーションを有効化します。 弾道は気温・気圧・湿度・重力・弾薬の種類・発射する武器などの変化による影響を受けるようになります。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>該模塊實現先進的彈道仿真 - 這意味著子彈的軌跡是由空氣溫度、大氣壓力、濕度、重力、彈藥類型以及射擊的武器所影響</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>该模块实现增强的弹道模拟—子弹的轨迹由空气温度、大气压力、湿度、重力、弹药类型和射击的武器等变量所影响</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Bu modül gelişmiş balistik simülasyonunu etkinleştirir - yani mermilerin gidişatını hava sıcaklığı, atmosfer basıncı, nem, yerçekimi, mühimmat türü ve ateşlendiği silah gibi durumlar etkiler.</Turkish>
            <Hungarian>Ez a modul engedélyezi a fejlett ballisztikai szimulációt - a lövedékek röppályáját befolyásolni fogja a levegő hőmérséklete, légnyomás, páratartalom, gravitáció, a lövedék fajtája, valamint a fegyver, amiből kilőtték a lövedéket.</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Цей модуль охоплює симуляцію розширеної балістики - водночас на траєкторію польоту снаряда впливають різні параметри, як-от температура повітря, атмосферний тиск, вологість, гравітація, тип боєприпасу і зброї, з якої зробили постріл.</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_DisplayName">
            <English>Advanced Ballistics</English>
            <Czech>Pokročilá balistika</Czech>
            <French>Balistique avancée</French>
            <Spanish>Balística avanzada</Spanish>
            <Italian>Balistica Avanzata</Italian>
            <Polish>Zaawansowana balistyka</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Balística avançada</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Продвинутая баллистика</Russian>
            <German>Erweiterte Ballistik</German>
            <Korean>고급 탄도학</Korean>
            <Japanese>高度な弾道計算</Japanese>
            <Chinese>先進彈道系統</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>进阶弹道系统</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Gelişmiş Balistik</Turkish>
            <Hungarian>Fejlett ballisztika</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Розширена балістика</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_ProtractorKey">
            <English>Show Protractor</English>
            <Czech>Zobrazit úhloměr</Czech>
            <French>Afficher le rapporteur</French>
            <Spanish>Mostrar transportador</Spanish>
            <Italian>Mostra il rapportatore</Italian>
            <Polish>Pokaż protraktor</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Mostrar Transferidor</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Показать транспортир</Russian>
            <German>Winkelmesser anzeigen</German>
            <Korean>각도기 표시</Korean>
            <Japanese>分度器を表示する</Japanese>
            <Chinese>顯示量角器</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>显示量角器</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Açı Ölçeri Göster</Turkish>
            <Hungarian>Szögmérő mutatása</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Показати транспортир</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_WindInfoKey">
            <English>Show Wind Info</English>
            <Czech>Zobrazit údaje o větru</Czech>
            <French>Afficher les infos sur le vent</French>
            <Spanish>Mostrar información del viento</Spanish>
            <Italian>Mostra indicazioni vento</Italian>
            <Polish>Pokaż inf. o wietrze</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Mostrar Informação do Vento</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Показать информацию о ветре</Russian>
            <German>Windinformationen anzeigen</German>
            <Korean>바람의 정보를 표시</Korean>
            <Japanese>風の情報を表示する</Japanese>
            <Chinese>顯示風況</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>显示风况</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Rüzgar bilgilerini göster</Turkish>
            <Hungarian>Széladatok mutatása</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Показати інформацію про вітер</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_ammoTemperatureEnabled_Description">
            <English>Muzzle velocity varies with ammo temperature</English>
            <Czech>Úsťová rychlost je závislá na teplotě munice</Czech>
            <French>La vitesse initiale varie en fonction de la température des munitions.</French>
            <Spanish>La velocidad de salida varía con la temperatura de la munición</Spanish>
            <Italian>La velocità alla volata varia a seconda della temperatura delle munizioni.</Italian>
            <Polish>Prędkość wylotowa pocisku jest zależna od temperatury amunicji</Polish>
            <Portuguese>A velocidade de saída varia com a temperatura da munição</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Начальная скорость пули зависит от температуры</Russian>
            <German>Munitionstemperatur hat Einfluss auf die Mündungsgeschwindigkeit</German>
            <Korean>탄약 온도에 비례해 총구 속도가 달라집니다</Korean>
            <Japanese>弾薬の温度により銃口初速を変動させます。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>子彈初速將隨彈藥溫度而有所變化</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>子弹初速将随弹药温度而有所变化</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Mermi çıkış hızı cephane sıcaklığına göre değişir</Turkish>
            <Hungarian>A kezdősebesség a lőszer hőmérsékletétől függően változó</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Початкова швидкість кулі залежить від температури</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_ammoTemperatureEnabled_DisplayName">
            <English>Enable Ammo Temperature Simulation</English>
            <Czech>Povolit simulaci teploty munice</Czech>
            <French>Activer la simulation de la température</French>
            <Spanish>Activar simulación de temperatura de munición</Spanish>
            <Italian>Abilita simulazione temperatura munizioni</Italian>
            <Polish>Symulacja temp. amunicji</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Ativar simulação de temperatura de munição</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Симуляция температуры для боеприпасов</Russian>
            <German>Simulation der Munitionstemperatur aktivieren</German>
            <Korean>탄약 온도 구현 적용</Korean>
            <Japanese>弾薬温度シミュレーションを有効化</Japanese>
            <Chinese>啟用彈藥溫度模擬系統</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>启用弹药温度模拟系统</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Cephane Sıcaklık Simülasyonunu Etkinleştir</Turkish>
            <Hungarian>Lőszer-hő szimuláció engedélyezése</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Симуляція температури для боєприпасів</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_barrelLengthInfluenceEnabled_Description">
            <English>Muzzle velocity varies with barrel length</English>
            <Czech>Úsťová rychlost je závislá na délce hlavně</Czech>
            <French>La vitesse initiale varie en fonction de la longueur du canon.</French>
            <Spanish>La velocidad de salidal varía con la longitud del cañón</Spanish>
            <Italian>La velocità alla volata varia a seconda della lunghezza della canna.</Italian>
            <Polish>Prędkość wylotowa pocisku jest zależna od długości lufy</Polish>
            <Portuguese>A velocidade de saída caria com o comprimento do cano</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Начальная скорость пули зависит от длины ствола</Russian>
            <German>Lauflänge beeinflusst Mündungsgeschwindigkeit</German>
            <Korean>총구 속도가 총열에 비례해 달라집니다</Korean>
            <Japanese>銃身長により銃口初速を変動させます。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>子彈初速將隨槍管長度而有所變化</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>子弹初速将随枪管长度而有所变化</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Mermi çıkış hızı namlu uzunluğuna göre değişir</Turkish>
            <Hungarian>A kezdősebesség a cső hosszától függően változó</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Початкова швидкість кулі залежить від довжини ствола</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_barrelLengthInfluenceEnabled_DisplayName">
            <English>Enable Barrel Length Simulation</English>
            <Czech>Povolit simulaci délky hlavně</Czech>
            <French>Activer la simulation de la longueur de canon</French>
            <Spanish>Habilitar la simulación de longitud del cañón</Spanish>
            <Italian>Abilita simulazione lunghezza canna</Italian>
            <Polish>Symulacja długości lufy</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Ativar a simulação de comprimento do cano</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Симуляция длины ствола</Russian>
            <German>Simulation der Lauflänge aktivieren</German>
            <Korean>총열 길이 구현 적용</Korean>
            <Japanese>銃身長シミュレーションを有効化</Japanese>
            <Chinese>啟用槍管長度模擬系統</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>启用枪管长度模拟系统</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Namlu Uzunluğu Simülasyonunu Etkinleştir</Turkish>
            <Hungarian>Csőhossz-szimuláció engedélyezése</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Симуляція довжини ствола</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_bulletTraceEnabled_Description">
            <English>Enables a bullet trace effect to high caliber bullets (only visible when looking through high power optics)</English>
            <Czech>Aktivuje efekt trasírek z vysokokaliberních zbraní (viditelné pouze skrze výkonnou optiku)</Czech>
            <French>Active un effet de balle traçante pour les munitions de gros calibre (seulement visible en utilisant une optique à fort grossissement).</French>
            <Spanish>Activa el efecto trazador de la balas de gran calibre (solo visible cuando se mira a través de una mira telescópica)</Spanish>
            <Italian>Abilita effetto di traccia lasciata da proiettili di alto calibro (visibile solo attraverso ottiche ad alto ingrandimento)</Italian>
            <Polish>Aktywuje efekt smugi pocisku dla pocisków wysokokalibrowych (widoczne tylko podczas patrzenia przez optykę)</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Ativa o efeito traçante de projétil para projéteis de alto calibre (somente visível quando observado por miras telescópicas)</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Включает эффект следов пуль для больших калибров (видны только через мощную оптику)</Russian>
            <German>Aktiviere Geschossspureffekt für hohe Kaliber (bei Benutzung von Optiken mit starker Vergrößerung)</German>
            <Korean>대구경 탄환에 예광탄 효과를 적용합니다(오직 고성능 조준경 사용시에만 보입니다)</Korean>
            <Japanese>大口径弾の軌跡エフェクトを有効化します。 (高性能光学機器を介してのみ見ることができます)</Japanese>
            <Chinese>啟用曳光彈效果給大口徑子彈 (只有透過高倍率光學瞄鏡才能看到)</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>给大口径子弹启用子弹尾迹效果（只有透过高倍率光学瞄镜才能看到）</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Yüksek kalibreli mermilere mermi izleme efekti sağlar (yalnızca yüksek güçlü optiklerden bakıldığında görülebilir)</Turkish>
            <Hungarian>Engedélyezi a nagy kaliberű lövedékek nyomának vizuális követését (csak nagy teljesítményű optikán keresztül látható)</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Включає ефект слідів куль для великих калібрів (видно тільки через потужну оптику)</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_bulletTraceEnabled_DisplayName">
            <English>Enable Bullet Trace Effect</English>
            <Czech>Povolit efekt trasírek</Czech>
            <French>Activer l'effet de balle traçante</French>
            <Spanish>Activar el efecto trazador de la bala</Spanish>
            <Italian>Abilita effetto di traccia proiettile</Italian>
            <Polish>Efekt smugi pocisku</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Ativa efeito traçante de projétil</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Следы пуль</Russian>
            <German>Geschossspureffekt aktivieren</German>
            <Korean>예광탄 효과 적용</Korean>
            <Japanese>弾丸の軌跡エフェクトを有効化</Japanese>
            <Chinese>啟用曳光彈效果</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>启用子弹尾迹效果</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>İzli Mermi Etkisini Etkinleştir</Turkish>
            <Hungarian>Nyomkövető-effekt engedélyezése</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Сліди куль</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_enabled_Description">
            <English>Enables advanced ballistics</English>
            <Czech>Aktivuje pokročilou balistiku</Czech>
            <French>Active la balistique avancée.</French>
            <Spanish>Activa la balística avanzada</Spanish>
            <Italian>Abilita Balistica Avanzata</Italian>
            <Polish>Aktywuje zaawansowaną balistykę</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Ativa a balística avançada</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Включает продвинутую баллистику</Russian>
            <German>Aktiviert die erweiterte Ballistik</German>
            <Korean>고급 탄도학을 적용합니다</Korean>
            <Japanese>高度な弾道計算を有効化します。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>啟用先進彈道系統</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>启用进阶弹道系统</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Gelişmiş balistiği etkinleştir</Turkish>
            <Hungarian>Engedélyezi a fejlett ballisztikát</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Вмикає розширену балістику</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_enabled_DisplayName">
            <English>Advanced Ballistics</English>
            <Czech>Pokročilá balistika</Czech>
            <French>Balistique avancée</French>
            <Spanish>Balística avanzada</Spanish>
            <Italian>Balistica Avanzata</Italian>
            <Polish>Zaawansowana balistyka</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Balística avançada</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Продвинутая баллистика</Russian>
            <German>Erweiterte Ballistik</German>
            <Korean>고급 탄도학</Korean>
            <Japanese>高度な弾道計算を有効化</Japanese>
            <Chinese>先進彈道系統</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>进阶弹道系统</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Gelişmiş Balistik</Turkish>
            <Hungarian>Fejlett ballisztika</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Розширена балістика</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_muzzleVelocityVariationEnabled_Description">
            <English>Simulates slight variations in muzzle velocity between each shot</English>
            <Czech>Simuluje malé odchylky v úsťové rychlosti mezi jednotlivými výstřely</Czech>
            <French>Simule de légères variations de vitesse initiale entre chaque tir.</French>
            <Spanish>Simula variaciones ligeras de velocidad entre cada disparo</Spanish>
            <Italian>Simula piccole variazioni della velocità alla volata tra ogni colpo.</Italian>
            <Polish>Symuluje lekkie zmiany w prędkości wylotowej między każdym strzałem</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Simula pequenas variações na velocidade do Freio de Boca entre cada tiro</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Имитирует небольшие изменения начальной скорости при каждом выстреле</Russian>
            <German>Simuliert leichte Variationen der Mündungsgeschwindigkeit zwischen jedem Schuss.</German>
            <Korean>각 사격 사이에 총구속도 변화를 시뮬레이션 합니다.</Korean>
            <Japanese>各発射毎の銃口初速のわずかな変動をシミュレートします。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>模擬每發子彈的槍口初速都略有不同</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>模拟每发子弹的枪口初速都略有不同</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Her atış arasında namlu çıkış hızındaki küçük değişiklikleri simüle eder</Turkish>
            <Ukrainian>Імітує невеликі зміни початкової швидкості під час кожного пострілу</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_muzzleVelocityVariationEnabled_DisplayName">
            <English>Enable Muzzle Velocity Variation</English>
            <Czech>Povoluje variantu rychlosti ústí</Czech>
            <French>Activer la variation de vitesse initiale</French>
            <Spanish>Activar variación de velocidad inicial</Spanish>
            <Italian>Abilita Variazione Velocità Volata</Italian>
            <Polish>Aktywuj wariację prędkości wylotowej</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Ativar Variação de Velocidade no Freio de boca</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Вкл. вариацию начальной скорости</Russian>
            <German>Variation der Mündungsgeschwindigkeit aktivieren</German>
            <Korean>총구속도 변화적용</Korean>
            <Japanese>銃口初速の変動を有効化</Japanese>
            <Chinese>啟用槍口初速變化</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>启用枪口初速变化</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Namlu Hızı Değişimini Etkinleştir</Turkish>
            <Ukrainian>Увімкнути варіацію початкової швидкості</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_simulationInterval_Description">
            <English>Defines the interval between each calculation step</English>
            <Czech>Určuje interval mezi každým výpočtem</Czech>
            <French>Définit l'intervalle entre chacune des étapes de calcul.</French>
            <Spanish>Define el intervalo entre cada cálculo</Spanish>
            <Italian>Definisce l'intervallo tra ogni passo del calcolo</Italian>
            <Polish>Określa interwał pomiędzy każdym krokiem kalkulacji</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Define o intervalo entre cada cálculo</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Определяет временной интервал между вычислениями</Russian>
            <German>Definiert das Intervall zwischen den einzelnen Simulationsschritten</German>
            <Korean>각 계산 단위의 간격을 정의합니다</Korean>
            <Japanese>各シミュレーション毎の間隔を定義します。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>定義每個模擬計算之間的時間間隔</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>定义每个计算步骤之间的间隔</Chinesesimp>
            <Hungarian>Meghatározza a számítási lépések közötti időintervallumot</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Визначає часовий інтервал між обчисленнями</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_simulationInterval_DisplayName">
            <English>Simulation Interval</English>
            <Czech>Interval simulace</Czech>
            <French>Intervalle de simulation</French>
            <Spanish>Intervalo de simulación</Spanish>
            <Italian>Intervallo di Simulazione</Italian>
            <Polish>Interwał symulacji</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Intervalo da simulação</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Интервал симуляции</Russian>
            <German>Simulationsintervall</German>
            <Korean>구현 간격</Korean>
            <Japanese>シミュレーション間隔</Japanese>
            <Chinese>模擬間隔</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>模拟间隔</Chinesesimp>
            <Hungarian>Szimuláció intervalluma</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Інтервал симуляції</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_simulationRadius_Description">
            <English>Defines the radius around the player (in meters) at which advanced ballistics are applied to projectiles</English>
            <Czech>Určuje oblast kolem hráče (v metrech), kde je pokročilá balistika použita na projektil</Czech>
            <French>Définit le rayon autour du joueur (en mètres), dans lequel la balistique avancée est appliquée aux projectiles.</French>
            <Spanish>Define el radio alrededor del jugador (en metros) en el cual se aplica la balística avanzada a los proyectiles</Spanish>
            <Italian>Definisce il raggio attorno al giocatore (in metri) entro il quale la Balistica Avanzata è applicata ai proiettili</Italian>
            <Polish>Określa obszar naokoło gracza (w metrach), na którym zaawansowana balistyka jest aplikowana dla pocisków</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Define o raio ao redor do jogador (em metros) onde a balística avançada será aplicada aos projéteis</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Определяет радиус вокруг игрока (в метрах), в котором продвинутая баллистика применяется к снарядам</Russian>
            <German>Gibt den Radius (in Metern) um den Spieler an, bei dem die erweiterte Ballistik auf Geschosse angewendet wird</German>
            <Korean>플레이어 주위의 발사체를 고급 탄도학으로 정의하는 범위를 정합니다(미터)</Korean>
            <Japanese>高度な弾道計算が飛翔体に適用される半径距離 (プレイヤー中心、メートル単位) を定義します。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>以玩家的半徑距離(公尺)定義先進彈道系統啟用範圍</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>定义玩家周围的半径（米），在这个半径内，进阶弹道系统会被启用</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Mermilere gelişmiş balistik uygulandığı oyuncunun etrafındaki yarıçapı (metre cinsinden) tanımlar</Turkish>
            <Hungarian>Meghatározza a játékos körüli hatókört (méterben), ahol a lövedékek fejlett ballisztikát használnak</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Визначає радіус навколо гравця (у метрах), у якому розширена балістика застосовується до снарядів</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Advanced_Ballistics_simulationRadius_DisplayName">
            <English>Simulation Radius</English>
            <Czech>Rozsah simulace</Czech>
            <French>Rayon de simulation</French>
            <Spanish>Radio de simulación</Spanish>
            <Italian>Raggio Simulazione</Italian>
            <Polish>Zasięg symulacji</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Raio da simulação</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Радиус симуляции</Russian>
            <German>Simulationsradius</German>
            <Korean>구현 범위</Korean>
            <Japanese>シミュレーションの半径</Japanese>
            <Chinese>模擬半徑</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>模拟半径</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Similasyon Yarıçapı</Turkish>
            <Hungarian>Szimuláció hatóköre</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Радіус симуляції</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>
