<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="ACE">
    <Package name="Headless">
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Headless_Module">
            <English>Headless</English>
            <German>Headless</German>
            <Polish>Headless</Polish>
            <Italian>Headless</Italian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Headless_ModuleDesc">
            <English>This module allows you to setup automatic transferring of AI to Headless Clients. (Default: No)</English>
            <German>Dieses Modul erlaubt es dir, die KI automatisch auf einen Headless Client zu transferieren. (Standard: Nein) </German>
            <Polish>Moduł ten pozwala ustawić automatyczne przenoszenie AI do Headless Clientów. (Domyślnie: Nie)</Polish>
            <Italian>Questo modulo ti consente di impostare il trasferimento automatico di IA all'Headless Client (Default: No)</Italian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Headless_EnabledDesc">
            <English>Enables transferring of AI to Headless Clients.</English>
            <German>Aktiviert den Transfer der KI auf Headless Clients.</German>
            <Polish>Aktywuje przenoszenie AI do Headless Clientów</Polish>
            <Italian>Abilita trasferimento di IA a Headless Client</Italian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Headless_Delay">
            <English>Delay</English>
            <German>Verzögerung</German>
            <Polish>Opóźnienie</Polish>
            <Italian>Ritardo</Italian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Headless_DelayDesc">
            <English>Minimal delay between transfers, in seconds. (Default: 15)</English>
            <German>Minimale Verzögerung zwischen Transfers in Sekunden. (Standard: 15)</German>
            <Polish>Minimalne opóźnienie w sekundach pomiędzy transferami. (Domyślnie: 15)</Polish>
            <Italian>Ritardo minimo tra trasferimenti, in secondi. (Default: 15)</Italian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Headless_Log">
            <English>Log</English>
            <German>Protokolldatei anlegen</German>
            <Polish>Dziennik</Polish>
            <Italian>Log</Italian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Headless_LogDesc">
            <English>Log transfer statistics and Headless Client (dis)connections to RPT. (Default: No)</English>
            <German>Zeichnet Transferstatistiken, Verbindungen und Verbindungsabbrüche in einer RPT-Datei auf. (Standard: Nein)</German>
            <Polish>Zapisuj statystyki transferów oraz status Headless Clienta do RPT. (Domyślnie: Nie)</Polish>
            <Italian>Logga statistiche trasferimenti e (dis)connessioni di Headless Client su RPT. (Default: No)</Italian>
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>