<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="ACE">
    <Package name="Hearing">
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_EarPlugs_Name">
            <English>Earplugs</English>
            <German>Ohrenstöpsel</German>
            <Spanish>Tapones para los oídos</Spanish>
            <Polish>Stopery do uszu</Polish>
            <Czech>Špunty</Czech>
            <Russian>Беруши</Russian>
            <French>Bouchons Anti-Bruits</French>
            <Hungarian>Füldugó</Hungarian>
            <Portuguese>Protetor auricular</Portuguese>
            <Italian>Tappi auricolari</Italian>
            <Japanese>耳栓</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_EarPlugs_Description">
            <English>Protective Earplugs allow the wearer to be near loud weaponry without damage to his hearing.</English>
            <German>Schützende Ohrenstöpsel, die es dem Träger ermöglichen, sich in der Nähe lauter Waffen aufzuhalten ohne Gehörschäden davonzutragen..</German>
            <Spanish>Los tapones para los oídos permiten al usuario operar armamento ruidoso sin sufrir pérdida de audición.</Spanish>
            <Polish>Stopery do uszu umożliwiają użytkownikowi przebywać w pobliżu głośnej broni bez poniesienia konsekwencji jaką jest utrata słuchu.</Polish>
            <Czech>Ochranné špunty umožňují uživateli, aby neutrpěl zranění jeho sluchu v blízkosti hlasitých zbraní.</Czech>
            <Russian>Беруши позволяют носителю находиться возле громкого вооружения без потери слуха.</Russian>
            <French>Bouchons Anti-Bruits permettant au porteur d'être près d'arme bruyante sans risque d'endommager son ouïe.</French>
            <Hungarian>Erősebb hanghatásoktól védő füldugó, megakadályozza a nagy hanggal járó fegyverzettől való halláskárosodást.</Hungarian>
            <Portuguese>Protetor para ouvidos permitem que o usuário esteja próximo a ruídos sem danificar sua audição.</Portuguese>
            <Italian>Proteggono l'apparato uditivo, permettendo a chi li indossa di resistere ai suoni particolarmente forti senza alcun danno.</Italian>
            <Japanese>着けることにより、近くの大きな銃声から聴覚を保護します。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_EarPlugs_On">
            <English>Earplugs in</English>
            <German>Ohrenstöpsel rein</German>
            <Spanish>Poner tapones</Spanish>
            <Polish>Włóż stopery</Polish>
            <Czech>Dát špunty do uší</Czech>
            <Russian>Надеть беруши</Russian>
            <French>Mettre les bouchons</French>
            <Hungarian>Füldugó berakva</Hungarian>
            <Portuguese>Protetores colocados</Portuguese>
            <Italian>Indossa i tappi auricolari</Italian>
            <Japanese>耳栓を着ける</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_EarPlugs_Off">
            <English>Earplugs out</English>
            <German>Ohrenstöpsel raus</German>
            <Spanish>Quitar tapones</Spanish>
            <Polish>Wyjmij stopery</Polish>
            <Czech>Vyndat špunty z uší</Czech>
            <Russian>Снять беруши</Russian>
            <French>Enlever les bouchons</French>
            <Hungarian>Füldugó kivéve</Hungarian>
            <Portuguese>Protetores retirados</Portuguese>
            <Italian>Levati i tappi auricolari</Italian>
            <Japanese>耳栓を外す</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_EarPlugs_Are_On">
            <English>Earplugs in</English>
            <German>Ohrenstöpsel drin</German>
            <Spanish>Tapones puestos</Spanish>
            <Polish>Stopery włożone</Polish>
            <Czech>Špunty v uších</Czech>
            <Russian>Беруши надеты</Russian>
            <French>Bouchons mis</French>
            <Hungarian>Füldugó berakva</Hungarian>
            <Portuguese>Protetores colocados</Portuguese>
            <Italian>Indossa i tappi auricolari</Italian>
            <Japanese>耳栓を着けた</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_EarPlugs_Are_Off">
            <English>Earplugs out</English>
            <German>Ohrenstöpsel raus</German>
            <Spanish>Tapones quitados</Spanish>
            <Polish>Stopery wyjęte</Polish>
            <Czech>Špunty venku z uší</Czech>
            <Russian>Беруши сняты</Russian>
            <French>Bouchons enlevés</French>
            <Hungarian>Füldugó kivéve</Hungarian>
            <Portuguese>Protetores retirados</Portuguese>
            <Italian>Levati i tappi auricolari</Italian>
            <Japanese>耳栓を外した</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_NoPlugs">
            <English>You have no earplugs</English>
            <German>Keine Ohrenstöpsel im Inventar</German>
            <Spanish>No tienes tapones para los oídos</Spanish>
            <Polish>Nie masz stoperów</Polish>
            <Czech>Nemáš žádné špunty</Czech>
            <Russian>У вас нет беруш</Russian>
            <French>Vous n'avez pas de bouchons anti-bruits</French>
            <Hungarian>Nincsen füldugód</Hungarian>
            <Portuguese>Você não possui protetores auriculares</Portuguese>
            <Italian>Non hai i tappi auricolari</Italian>
            <Japanese>耳栓を持っていません</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_Inventory_Full">
            <English>No inventory space</English>
            <German>Kein Platz im Inventar</German>
            <Spanish>Sin espacio en el inventario</Spanish>
            <Polish>Brak miejsca w ekwipunku</Polish>
            <French>Pas de place dans l'inventaire</French>
            <Czech>Není místo v inventáři</Czech>
            <Italian>Non hai abbastanza spazio</Italian>
            <Portuguese>Não há espaço no inventário</Portuguese>
            <Hungarian>Nincs több hely</Hungarian>
            <Russian>Нет места в инвентаре</Russian>
            <Japanese>インベントリに空きがありません。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_DisableEarRinging_DisplayName">
            <English>Disable ear ringing</English>
            <French>Désactiver le bourdonnement</French>
            <Spanish>Desactivar zumbido de oídos</Spanish>
            <Russian>Отключить звон в ушах</Russian>
            <German>Knalltrauma deaktivieren</German>
            <Czech>Vypnout pískání v uších</Czech>
            <Polish>Wyłącz dzwonienie w uszach</Polish>
            <Hungarian>Fülcsengés letiltása</Hungarian>
            <Italian>Disabilita i fischi nelle orecchie</Italian>
            <Portuguese>Desabilitar zumbido de ouvidos</Portuguese>
            <Japanese>耳鳴りを無効化する</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_DisableEarRinging_Description">
            <English>Remove tinnitus effect when the player takes hearing damage</English>
            <German>Deaktiviert Ohrklingeln wenn der Spieler Hörschäden davonträgt.</German>
            <Spanish>Desactiva el efecto de zumbido cuando el jugador recibe daño auditivo.</Spanish>
            <Polish>Usuń szum w uszach przy chwilowej utracie słuchu.</Polish>
            <French>Enlève les acouphènes quand le joueur prend des dommages auditifs.</French>
            <Italian>Quando il giocatore riceve danni all'udito, non fa sentire i fischi nelle orecchie</Italian>
            <Portuguese>Remove o efeito de zunido quando o jogador recebe dano na audição</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Убирает эффект звона в ушах, когда игрок получает повреждение слуха</Russian>
            <Japanese>プレイヤーの聴覚が損傷をしたら耳鳴りの効果を削除します</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_Module_DisplayName">
            <English>Hearing</English>
            <Polish>Słuch</Polish>
            <Spanish>Audición</Spanish>
            <German>Gehör</German>
            <Czech>Sluch</Czech>
            <Portuguese>Audição</Portuguese>
            <French>Audition</French>
            <Hungarian>Hallás</Hungarian>
            <Russian>Слух</Russian>
            <Italian>Udito</Italian>
            <Japanese>聴覚</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_EnableCombatDeafness_DisplayName">
            <English>Enable Combat Deafness</English>
            <Polish>Wł. głuchotę bojową</Polish>
            <Spanish>Habilitar sordera de combate</Spanish>
            <German>Aktiviere Taubheit im Gefecht?</German>
            <Czech>Povolit ztrátu sluchu?</Czech>
            <Portuguese>Ativar surdez em combate?</Portuguese>
            <French>Activer la surdité au combat</French>
            <Hungarian>Harci süketség engedélyezése?</Hungarian>
            <Russian>Оглушение</Russian>
            <Italian>Sordità da combattimento</Italian>
            <Japanese>戦闘による難聴を有効化</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_EnableCombatDeafness_Description">
            <English>Reduces the hearing ability as the player takes hearing damage</English>
            <Polish>Możliwość chwilowej utraty słuchu przy głośnych wystrzałach i jednoczesnym braku włożonych stoperów</Polish>
            <Spanish>Habilita la sordera de combate</Spanish>
            <German>Verringert das Hörvermögen wenn der Spieler einen Hörschaden davonträg</German>
            <Czech>Snižuje schopnost sluchu pokud dojde k jeho poškození hlasitou a blízkou střelbou</Czech>
            <Portuguese>Ativar surdez em combate?</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Уменьшает возможность игрока слышать звуки при повреждении органов слуха</Russian>
            <Italian>Riduci l'abilità uditiva quando il giocatore riceve danno uditivo</Italian>
            <French>Réduire l'audition lorsque le joueur prend des dommages auditifs.</French>
            <Japanese>音による損傷をうけ、聴覚が減る可能性があります</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_Module_Description">
            <English>Controls combat deafness and ear ringing. When activated, players can be deafened when a gun is fired in their vicinity or an explosion takes place without hearing protection</English>
            <Hungarian>Harci süketség engedélyezése?</Hungarian>
            <Russian>Уменьшает способность игроков слышать при повреждении слуха</Russian>
            <Polish>Głuchota bojowa pojawia się w momentach, kiedy stoimy w pobliżu broni wielkokalibrowej bez ochrony słuchu, lub np. podczas ostrzału artyleryjskiego. Moduł ten pozwala na włączenie lub wyłączenie tego efektu.</Polish>
            <German>Dieses Modul aktiviert/deaktiviert die Taubheit im Gefecht. Wenn aktiviert, können Spieler ohne Gehörschutz taub werden, wenn eine Waffe in ihrer Nähe abgefeuert wird oder eine Explosion stattfindet.</German>
            <Czech>Ztráta sluchu je možná ve chvíly, kdy se v bezprostřední blízkosti střílí z velkorážní zbraně nebo při bombardování a osoba je  bez ochrany sluchu (např. špunty). Tento modul umožňuje tuto věc povolit nebo zakázat.</Czech>
            <Portuguese>Este módulo ativa / desativa surdez em combate. Quando ativado, os jogadores podem ficar surdos quando uma arma é disparada ao seu redor ou uma explosão ocorre sem proteção auditiva.</Portuguese>
            <French>Ce module active / désactivé la surdité au combat. Si active, des joueurs peuvent devenir sourds sans protection d'oreille, si une arme est utilisée ou une explosion a lieu à proximité</French>
            <Spanish>Controles de sordera de combate y zumbido en los oídos. Al activarlo, los jugadores pueden ser ensordecidos cuando un arma se dispara cerca o una explosión tiene lugar sin protección auditiva</Spanish>
            <Italian>Controlla la sordità da combattimento e fischio alle orecchie. Quando attivato, i giocatori possono essere assordati quando un'arma spara vicino o avviene un'esplosione senza protezione uditiva</Italian>
            <Japanese>戦闘による難聴や、耳鳴りを設定します。有効になった場合、聴覚を保護していないと近傍の銃声や爆発音により、難聴になります。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_enabledForZeusUnits_DisplayName">
            <English>Effect Zeus RC</English>
            <German>Beeinflusst Zeus-Einheiten</German>
            <Polish>Wpływ na Zeus RC</Polish>
            <Russian>Влияет на юнита Зевса</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Afeta Zeus CR</Portuguese>
            <Spanish>Efecto Zeus RC</Spanish>
            <Czech>Vliv na Zeus RC</Czech>
            <Italian>Effetto Zeus RC</Italian>
            <French>Effet sur le CàD du Zeus</French>
            <Japanese>Zeus RC への効果</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_enabledForZeusUnits_Description">
            <English>Allow zeus remote controlled units to be able to take hearing damage.</English>
            <German>Erlaubt, durch von Zeus gesteuerten Einheiten, einen Hörschaden davonzutragen.</German>
            <Polish>Aktywuj efekty utraty słuchu dla jednostek kontrolowanych zdalnie przez Zeusa.</Polish>
            <Russian>Контролирует оглушение в бою и звон в ушах. При активации играки могут быть оглушены близкими выстрелами и взрывами при отсутствии защиты для ушей.</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Permite que unidades remotamente controladas pelo Zeus sejam atingidas por danos auditivos.</Portuguese>
            <Spanish>Permitir a las unidades por control remoto de zeus que puedan tener daños auditivos.</Spanish>
            <Czech>Aktivovat efekt ztráty sluchu pro vzdáleně ovládané jednotky.</Czech>
            <Italian>Consenti alle unità controllate in remoto da Zeus di ricevere danni all'udito.</Italian>
            <French>Permet aux unités controlées à distance de subir des traumatismes sonores.</French>
            <Japanese>Zeus により遠隔操作されたユニットにも、聴覚へ損傷を受けるようにします。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_autoAddEarplugsToUnits_DisplayName">
            <English>Add earplugs to units</English>
            <German>Füge Ohrenstöpsel zu Einheiten hinzu</German>
            <Polish>Dodaj stopery dla jednostek</Polish>
            <Russian>Добавлять юнитам беруши</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Adiciona protetores de ouvido as unidades</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Přidat špunty jednotce</Czech>
            <Italian>Aggiungi Tappi per Orecchie alle unità</Italian>
            <Spanish>Agregar tapones de oida a la unidad</Spanish>
            <French>Ajouter des bouchons anti-bruits aux unités</French>
            <Japanese>ユニットへ耳栓を追加</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Hearing_autoAddEarplugsToUnits_Description">
            <English>Add the `ACE_EarPlugs` item to all units that have loud weapons. Can disable if using custom loadouts.</English>
            <German>Fügt die "ACE_EarPlugs" zu allen Einheiten mit lauten Waffen hinzu. Wird deaktiviert wenn eine eigene Inventarkonfiguration vorgenommen wurde.</German>
            <Polish>Dodaje `ACE_EarPlugs` -  stopery - do wszystkich jednostek, które posiadają głośną broń. Można wyłaczyć w przypadku korzystania z niestandardowych loadoutów.</Polish>
            <Russian>Добавляет предмет `ACE_EarPlugs` всем юнитам, которые имеют громкое оружие. Можно отключить при ручной настройке снаряжения.</Russian>
            <Portuguese>Adicionar o item `ACE_EarPlugs` a todas as unidades que tenham armas barulhentas. Pode ser desabilitado com carregamentos customizados.</Portuguese>
            <Czech>Přidat `ACE_EarPlugs` všem jednotkám které mají zbraň. Můžete vypnout, pokud používáte vlastní výbavu.</Czech>
            <Italian>Aggiungi l'oggetto 'ACE_EarPlugs' a tutte le unità che hanno armi rumorose. Può essere disabilitato se vengono usati loadout personalizzati.</Italian>
            <Spanish>Agregar el item `ACE_EarPlugs`  a todas las unidades equipadas con armas muy ruidosas. Desactivar si quieren utilizarse equipamientos personalizados.</Spanish>
            <French>Ajoute l'objet "Ace_EarPlugs" à toutes les unités ayant des armes bruyantes. Peut être désactivé par des loadouts personalisés.</French>
            <Japanese>全ユニットへ`ACE_EarPlugs`アイテムをもたせます。これは変更された武装で無効化できます。</Japanese>
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>