<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="ACE">
    <Package name="Slideshow">
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Slideshow_DisplayName">
            <English>Slideshow</English>
            <Czech>Prezentace</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Slideshow_Description">
            <English>This module allows you to set up slide-shows on different objects. One module per image list. Only objects with hiddenSelection 0 are supported.</English>
            <Czech>Tento modul umožňuje nastavit prezentaci na různých objektech. Jeden modul na každý seznam obrázků. Pouze objekty s hiddenSelection 0 jsou podporovány.</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Slideshow_Objects_DisplayName">
            <English>Objects</English>
            <Czech>Objekty</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Slideshow_Objects_Description">
            <English>Object names (can also be synchronized objects) slide-show will be displayed on, separated by commas if multiple. Reference INFO for object support.</English>
            <Czech>Jména objektů (mohou být také synchronizované objekty) na kterých bude prezentace zobrazena, oddělené čárkami pokud jich je více. Referenční INFO pro podporu objeků.</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Slideshow_Controllers_DisplayName">
            <English>Controllers</English>
            <Czech>Ovladače</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Slideshow_Controllers_Description">
            <English>Controller object names, separated by commas if multiple.</English>
            <Czech>Jména ovladače objektu, oddělené čárkami pokud jich je více.</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Slideshow_Images_DisplayName">
            <English>Images</English>
            <Czech>Obrázky</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Slideshow_Images_Description">
            <English>List of images that will be used for the slide-show, separated by commas, with full path correctly formatted (eg. images\image.paa).</English>
            <Czech>Seznam obrázků, které budou použity pro prezentaci, oddělené čárkami, s celou cestou ve správném formátu (např. images\image.paa).</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Slideshow_Names_DisplayName">
            <English>Interaction Names</English>
            <Czech>Interakce jmen</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Slideshow_Names_Description">
            <English>List of names that will be used for interaction entries, separated by commas, in order of images.</English>
            <Czech>Seznam jmen, které budou použity pro položky interakce, oddělené čárkami, v pořadí obrázků.</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Slideshow_Duration_DisplayName">
            <English>Slide Duration</English>
            <Czech>Trvání snímku</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Slideshow_Duration_Description">
            <English>Duration of each slide. Default: 0 (Automatic Transitions Disabled)</English>
            <Czech>Doba trvání každého snímku. Výchozí: 0 (Zakázány automatické přechody)</Czech>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Slideshow_Interaction">
            <English>Slides</English>
            <Czech>Snímky</Czech>
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>