<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="ACE">
    <Package name="Medical_Statemachine">
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Medical_Statemachine_AIUnconsciousness_Description">
            <English>Controls whether AI can go unconscious instead of immediately dying.\nThis setting works together with the "AI Fatal Injuries" setting since, going into cardiac arrest requires that the unit is able to go unconscious.\nHowever, these settings are separated because units can go unconscious from critical vitals resulting from non-fatal injuries.\nIn essence, this means that in order to enable cardiac arrest for AI units, this setting must be enabled.</English>
            <Czech>Nastavuje zda AI může upadnout do bezvědomí namísto okamžité smrti.\nToto nastavení funguje společně s "Smrtelná zranění AI" protože srdeční zástava potřebuje možnost upadnout do bezvědomí.\nTyto možnosti jsou separované, protože jednotky mohou upadnout do bezvědomí kvůli kritickému stavu způsobenému ne smrtelnými zraněními.\nV podstatě to znamená, že pokud chcete zapnout srdeční zástavu pro AI, tato možnost musí být zapnutá.</Czech>
            <French>Définit si les unités IA peuvent perdre connaissance au lieu de mourir immédiatement.\nCe paramètre fonctionne conjointement avec l'option "Décès si blessure mortelle (IA)" car, pour qu'une unité IA subisse un arrêt cardiaque, elle doit également pouvoir perdre connaissance.\nCependant, ces paramètres sont séparés car les unités peuvent s'évanouir suite à des signes vitaux critiques résultant de blessures non mortelles.\nEn résumé, cela signifie que ce paramètre doit absolument être activé pour qu'une unité IA puisse entrer en état d'arrêt cardiaque.</French>
            <Spanish>Controla si la IA puede quedar inconsciente en lugar de morir de inmediato. \n Esta configuración funciona junto con la configuración de "Heridas mortales IA", ya que, sufrir un paro cardíaco requiere que la unidad pueda quedar inconsciente. \n Sin embargo, estas configuraciones están separadas porque las unidades pueden perder el conocimiento de los signos vitales críticos como resultado de lesiones no mortales. \n En esencia, esto significa que para habilitar el paro cardíaco en las unidades de IA, esta configuración debe estar habilitada.</Spanish>
            <Italian>Controlla se l'IA può perdere i sensi invece di morire immediatamente. Questa impostazione funziona insieme all'impostazione "Ferite letali IA" poiché, per andare in arresto cardiaco, è necessario che l'unità sia in grado di perdere i sensi. Tuttavia, queste impostazioni sono separate perché le unità possono perdere i sensi da segni vitali critici derivanti da ferite non letali.</Italian>
            <Polish>Definiuje, czy AI może stracić przytomność zamiast natychmiast zginąć.\n Ta opcja działa razem z ustawieniem "Śmiertelne urazy AI", ponieważ przejście do zatrzymania akcji serca wymaga, aby jednostka mogła stracić przytomność.\n Jednak te ustawienia są rozdzielone, ponieważ jednostki mogą stracić przytomność z powodu krytycznych czynności życiowych powstałych w wyniku urazów innych niż śmiertelne.\n W istocie oznacza to, że aby umożliwić zatrzymanie akcji serca dla jednostek AI, to ustawienie musi być włączone.</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Controla se a IA pode ficar inconsciente ao invés de morrer imediatamente.\nEssa configuração funciona com "Lesões Fatais de IA", pois para uma unidade ter uma parada cardíaca é necessário que a IA possa fica inconsciente.\nContudo, essas configurações são separadas pois unidades podem ficar inconscientes por vitais críticos causados por ferimentos não-fatais.\nEssencialmente, isso significa que para ativar uma parada cardíaca em IA, essa configuração precisa estar ativa.</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Управляет тем, может ли ИИ потерять сознание, вместо того, чтобы немедленно умереть.\nЭтот параметр работает вместе с параметром «Смертельные раны ИИ», поскольку при остановке сердца требуется, чтобы юнит мог потерять сознание.\nОднако эти настройки разделены, потому что юниты могут потерять сознание из-за критических ранений жизненно важных органов, полученных в результате несмертельных травм.\nВ сущности, это означает, что для включения остановки сердца для ИИ этот параметр должен быть включен.</Russian>
            <German>Kontrolliert, ob KI bewusstlos werden kann anstatt sofort zu sterben.\nDiese Einstellung funktioniert zusammen mit der Einstellung "Tödliche KI-Verletzungen". Denn wenn eine Einheit einen Herzstillstand erleiden soll, muss diese auch in der Lage sein, bewusstlos zu werden.\nDennoch sind diese beiden Einstellungen voneinander getrennt, da Einheiten auch durch kritische Vitalwerte bewusstlos werden können, die durch nicht tödliche Verletzungen aufgetreten sind.\nZusammengefasst bedeutet das, dass wenn KI-Einheiten einen Herzstillstand erleiden sollen, diese Einstellung aktiviert sein muss.</German>
            <Korean>AI가 즉시 죽는 대신 의식불명이 되는지 여부를 제어합니다.\n이 설정은 "인공지능 중태" 설정과 함께 작동합니다. 심정지가 발생하려면 유닛이 의식불명이 되어야 하기 때문입니다.\n그러나 이런 설정들은 비치명적인 부상으로 인해 치명적인 상태로 의식불명이 될 수 있기 때문에 분리되어 있습니다.\n기본적으로 이는 AI 유닛에 대한 심정지를 활성화하려면 이 설정을 활성화 해야함을 의미합니다.</Korean>
            <Japanese>AIが即死する代わりに無意識状態化するかどうかを制御します。\nこれは "AIの致命傷" 設定と連動します。何故ならば、ユニットを心停止させるためには無意識状態に陥る必要がある為です。\nしかし、これらの設定は、致命的ではない負傷の経過による重症状態化でユニットが無意識状態に陥ることが出来るようにするため、分割されています。\n要するに、AIユニットの心停止を有効にするには、この設定を有効にする必要があるということです。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>控制AI是否能進入無意識狀態而非立刻原地死亡。\n這個選項會與「AI致命傷」的選項聯動，使單位心搏停止的話必須先讓其無意識。\n然而，兩個設定分開之原因是使單位能因從非致命傷的攻擊情況下進入生命危險的狀態。\n簡單來說，你想要讓AI單位有心搏停止可能的話，該選項必須啟用。</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>控制 AI 是否可以进入昏迷状态而不是立即死亡。\n这个设置与"AI 致命伤"设置一起工作，因为进入心脏骤停需要单位能够昏迷。\n然而，这些设置是分开的，因为单位可能会因非致命伤害导致的关键生命体征而昏迷过去。\n从本质上讲，这意味着为了使 AI 单位的心脏骤停，必须启用此设置。</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Yapay zekanın hemen ölmek yerine bilinçsiz duruma geçip geçemeyeceğini kontrol eder. \ Bu ayar, "Yapay Zeka Ölümcül Yaralanmalar" ayarı ile birlikte çalışır, çünkü kalp durması, ünitenin bilinçsiz duruma geçebilmesini gerektirir. \ Özünde, bunun anlamı şudur: AI birimleri için kalp durmasını etkinleştirirseniz, bu ayar etkinleştirilmelidir.</Turkish>
            <Ukrainian>Керує тим, чи може ШІ знепритомніти, замість того, щоб негайно померти. Цей параметр працює разом із параметром "Смертельні рани ШІ", оскільки під час зупинки серця потрібно, щоб юніт міг знепритомніти. Проте ці параметри розділено, оскільки юніти можуть знепритомніти через критичні поранення життєво важливих органів, отримані внаслідок несмертельних травм. По суті, це означає, що для ввімкнення зупинки серця для ШІ цей параметр потрібно ввімкнути.</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Medical_Statemachine_AIUnconsciousness_DisplayName">
            <English>AI Unconsciousness</English>
            <Czech>Bezvědomí AI</Czech>
            <French>Inconscience IA</French>
            <Spanish>Inconsciencia IA</Spanish>
            <Italian>Incoscienza IA</Italian>
            <Polish>Nieprzytomność AI</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Inconsciência da IA</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Потеря сознания ботами</Russian>
            <German>KI-Bewusstlosigkeit</German>
            <Korean>인공지능 기절</Korean>
            <Japanese>AIの無意識状態化</Japanese>
            <Chinese>AI無意識</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>AI 无意识</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Yapay Zeka Bilinci</Turkish>
            <Hungarian>AI eszméletlenség</Hungarian>
            <Ukrainian>Втрата свідомості ШІ</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Medical_Statemachine_CardiacArrestBleedout_Description">
            <English>Controls whether a person can die in cardiac arrest by blood loss before the cardiac arrest time runs out.</English>
            <French>Définit si un joueur en arrêt cardiaque peut mourir par exsanguination, avant que la durée de l'arrêt cardiaque définie ci-dessus ne soit écoulée.</French>
            <Spanish>COntrola si una persona puede morir en parada cardíaca por causa de pérdida de sangre antes de que se termine el contador de parada cardíaca</Spanish>
            <Italian>Determina se è possibile morire per eccessiva perdita di sangue anche se non è ancora scaduto il 'tempo d'arresto cardiaco'.</Italian>
            <Polish>Kontroluje czy śmierć osoby może nastąpić poprzez wykrwawienie zanim wyczerpię się Czas Zatrzymania Akcji Serca.</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Controla se uma pessoa pode morrer em parada cardíaca por perda de sangue antes que o tempo de parada cardíaca acabe.</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Определяет, можно ли умереть от потери крови во время остановки сердца, даже если время жизни при остановке сердца еще не истекло.</Russian>
            <German>Legt fest, ob man während des Herzstillstands durch Blutverlust sterben kann, auch wenn die Überlebenszeit im Herzstillstand noch nicht ausgelaufen ist.</German>
            <Korean>지정한 심정지 시간이 다 되기 전에 출혈로 인해 사망할 수 있는 지를 결정합니다.</Korean>
            <Japanese>心停止中の失血によって心停止時間よりも早く死亡するかどうかを制御します。</Japanese>
            <Chinesesimp>控制单位是否会在心脏骤停时间耗完之前因失血过多而死亡。</Chinesesimp>
            <Ukrainian>Визначає, чи можна померти від втрати крові під час зупинки серця, навіть якщо час життя при зупинці серця ще не минув.</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Medical_Statemachine_CardiacArrestBleedout_DisplayName">
            <English>Bleedout During Cardiac Arrest</English>
            <French>Saignement durant l'arrêt cardiaque</French>
            <Spanish>Desangrado durante parada cardíaca</Spanish>
            <Italian>Dissanguamento in arresto cardiaco</Italian>
            <Polish>Wykrwawienie podczas zatrzymanej akcji serca</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Sangramento durante parada cardíaca</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Кровотечение во время остановки сердца</Russian>
            <German>Ausbluten im Herzstillstand</German>
            <Korean>심정지 중 출혈</Korean>
            <Japanese>心停止中の失血死</Japanese>
            <Chinesesimp>心脏骤停期间失血情况</Chinesesimp>
            <Ukrainian>Кровотеча під час зупинки серця</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Medical_Statemachine_CardiacArrestTime_Description">
            <English>Controls how long it takes to die from cardiac arrest.</English>
            <Czech>Nastavuje po jak dlouhé době pacient zemře kvůli srdeční zástavě.</Czech>
            <French>Définit le temps qu'il faut pour mourir d'un arrêt cardiaque.</French>
            <Spanish>Controla cuanto tiempo dura el paro cardiaco antes de morir.</Spanish>
            <Italian>Determina quanto tempo ci vuole per morire di arresto cardiaco.</Italian>
            <Polish>Definiuje czas potrzebny na śmierć z powodu zatrzymania akcji serca.</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Controla o tempo necessário para morrer para uma parada cardíaca.</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Контролирует, сколько времени требуется, чтобы умереть от остановки сердца.</Russian>
            <German>Bestimmt die Dauer bis zum Tod durch Herzstillstand.</German>
            <Korean>심정지 후 얼마나 지나야 죽는지 결정합니다.</Korean>
            <Japanese>どのくらいの時間、心停止すると死亡するかを制御します。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>控制心搏停止後多久死亡</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>控制心脏骤停后多久单位死亡</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Ne kadar süre de kalbi durarak ölmesini belirleyin.</Turkish>
            <Ukrainian>Контролює, скільки часу потрібно, щоб померти від зупинки серця.</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Medical_Statemachine_CardiacArrestTime_DisplayName">
            <English>Cardiac Arrest Time</English>
            <Czech>Délka srdeční zástavy</Czech>
            <French>Durée de l'arrêt cardiaque</French>
            <Spanish>Tiempo de paro cardíaco</Spanish>
            <Italian>Tempo d'arresto cardiaco</Italian>
            <Polish>Czas Zatrzymania Akcji Serca</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Tempo de Parada Cardíaca</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Длительность остановки сердца</Russian>
            <German>Überlebenszeit im Herzstillstand</German>
            <Korean>심정지 시간</Korean>
            <Japanese>心停止時間</Japanese>
            <Chinese>心搏停止時間</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>心脏骤停时间</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Kalp Durma Süresi</Turkish>
            <Ukrainian>Тривалість зупинки серця</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Medical_Statemachine_FatalInjuriesAI_Description">
            <English>Controls when AI can receive fatal injuries. A fatal injury is caused by significant damage to the head or troso.\nWhen set to "Always", this effectively produces "AI Instant Death" behaviour as AI will immediately die from any fatal injury.\nNOTE: Any mode other than "Always" requires AI Unconsciousness to be enabled.</English>
            <Czech>Nastavuje zda AI může utrpět smrtelné zranění. Smrtelné zranění je utrpěto významným poškozením hlavy nebo trupu.\nPokud je tato možnost nastavena na "Vždy", efektivně nastává stav "Povolit okamžitou smrt AI", protože AI okamžitě zemře při jakémkoliv smrtelném zranění.\nPOZNÁMKA: Jakýkoliv jiný stav než "Vždy" potřebuje zapnutou možnost "Bezvědomí AI".</Czech>
            <French>Détermine si les unités IA décèdent en cas de blessure mortelle. Une blessure mortelle est définie par des dommages importants à la tête ou au cœur.\nSi réglé sur "Toujours", cela produit effectivement un comportement de "Mort instantanée" car les unités IA mourront immédiatement de toute blessure mortelle.\nNOTE : Tout mode autre que "Toujours" nécessite l'activation de l'option "Inconscience IA".</French>
            <Spanish>Controla cuándo la IA puede sufrir lesiones fatales. Una lesión fatal es causada por un daño significativo en la cabeza o el cuerpo. \n Cuando se establece en "Siempre", esto produce efectivamente un comportamiento de "Muerte instantánea de IA", ya que la IA morirá inmediatamente por cualquier lesión fatal. \n NOTA: Cualquier modo que no sea "Siempre" requiere que la inconsciencia de la IA esté habilitada.</Spanish>
            <Italian>Controlla quando l'IA può ricevere infortuni mortali. Una ferita letale è causata da un danno significativo alla testa o al torso.\nSe impostato su "Sempre", questo produce efficacemente il comportamento "Morte istantanea AI", poiché l'IA morirà immediatamente a causa di qualsiasi lesione mortale.\nNOTA: Qualsiasi modalità diversa da "Sempre" richiede l'attivazione dell'Incoscienza IA.</Italian>
            <Polish>Definiuje, kiedy AI może otrzymać śmiertelne obrażenia. Śmiertelne obrażenia są spowodowane znacznym uszkodzeniem głowy lub torsu.\n Ustawienie "Zawsze" powoduje "Natychmiastową śmierć AI", ponieważ AI natychmiast umiera z powodu śmiertelnych obrażeń.\n UWAGA: Każdy inny tryb niż "Zawsze" wymaga włączenia nieprzytomności AI.</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Controla quando a IA pode receber lesões fatais. Uma lesão fatal é causada por um dano significante na cabeça ou tronco.\nQuando definido para "Sempre", isso efetivamente causa a "Morte Instantânea da IA", pois a IA irá imediatamente morrer para qualquer lesão fatal.\nNOTA: Qualquer opção além de "Sempre" requer que Inconsciência de IA esteja ativada.</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Определяет могут ли игроки получить смертельные травмы. Смертельная травма вызывается значительным повреждением головы или туловища.\nКогда установлено «Всегда», это вызывает поведение «Мгновенной смерти ИИ», так как ИИ немедленно умрет от любой смертельной травмы.\nПРИМЕЧАНИЕ: Любой режим, кроме «Всегда», требует включения функции «Потеря сознания».</Russian>
            <German>Legt fest, wann KI-Einheiten tödliche Verletzungen erleiden können. Eine tödliche Verletzung wird bei erheblichem Schaden an Kopf oder Körper verursacht.\nWenn "Immer" eingestellt ist, erzeugt diese Einstellung das "KI Sofort-Tod" Verhalten. KI-Einheiten sterben sofort durch jede tödliche Verletzung.\nBEACHTE: Eine andere Einstellung als "Immer" bedingt, dass "KI-Bewusstlosigkeit" verwendet wird.</German>
            <Korean>인공지능이 언제 중태로 빠질 지 결정합니다. 중태는 머리나 몸통에 심각한 피해를 입는 경우 발생합니다.\n "언제나"로 설정하면 "인공지능 즉사" 기능이 즉각 적용됩니다.\n 참고: "언제나"를 제외한 다른 모드는 인공지능의 기절이 활성화가 필요합니다.</Korean>
            <Japanese>AIが致命傷を受けた時の挙動を管理できます。頭部や胸部に受ける大きなダメージは致命傷になります。\n"常に"に設定されていると、いかなる致命傷でも"AIの即死"効果が生まれます。\n注: "常に"以外のモードでは"AIの無意識状態化"を有効化させる必要があります。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>控制當AI受致命傷時是否能救起。致命傷是指對頭部或身體造成可觀傷害所造成的。\n當設置為"總是"時，這會使其與"AI 瞬間死亡"同一個效果，在AI受到致命傷時瞬間死亡。\n備註：選了"總是"以外的選項的話必須開啟「AI無意識」的選項。</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>控制当 AI 受致命伤时是否能救起。致命伤是指对头部或躯干遭受重大伤害。\n当设置为"总是"时，这将有效地产生"AI 即时死亡"行为，因为 AI 将立即死于任何致命伤。\n注意："总是"以外的任何模式都需要启用 AI 无意识。</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>AI'nın ölümcül yaralanmaları ne zaman alabileceğini kontrol eder. Ölümcül bir yaralanma, kafa veya vücudun önemli hasar görmesinden kaynaklanır. \n"Her zaman" olarak ayarlandığında, AI herhangi bir ölümcül yaralanmadan hemen öleceği için bu etkili bir şekilde "AI Anında Ölüm" davranışı üretir.\n NOT: "Her zaman" "Yapay Zeka Bilinci'nin etkinleştirilmesini gerektirir.</Turkish>
            <Ukrainian>Визначає, чи можуть гравці отримати смертельні травми. Смертельна травма спричиняється значним ушкодженням голови або торсу.\nКоли встановлено "Завжди", це спричиняє поведінку "Миттєвої смерті ШІ", оскільки ШІ негайно помре від будь-якої смертельної травми.\nПРИМІТКА: Будь-який режим, окрім "Завжди", вимагає ввімкнення функції "Втрата свідомості".</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Medical_Statemachine_FatalInjuriesAI_DisplayName">
            <English>AI Fatal Injuries</English>
            <Czech>Smrtelná zranění AI</Czech>
            <French>Décès si blessure mortelle (IA)</French>
            <Spanish>Heridas mortales IA</Spanish>
            <Italian>Ferite letali su IA</Italian>
            <Polish>Śmiertelne obrażenia AI.</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Lesões Fatais da IA</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Смертельные травмы ИИ</Russian>
            <German>Tödliche KI-Verletzungen</German>
            <Korean>인공지능 중태</Korean>
            <Japanese>AIの致命傷</Japanese>
            <Chinese>AI致命傷</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>AI 致命伤</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>AI Ölümcül Yaralanmaları</Turkish>
            <Ukrainian>Смертельні травми ШІ</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Medical_Statemachine_FatalInjuriesPlayer_Description">
            <English>Controls when players can receive fatal injuries. A fatal injury is caused by significant damage to the head or torso.</English>
            <Czech>Nastavuje zda hráči mohou utrpět smrtelné zranění. Smrtelné zranění je utrpěto významným poškozením hlavy nebo trupu.</Czech>
            <French>Détermine si les joueurs décèdent en cas de blessure mortelle. Une blessure mortelle est définie par des dommages importants à la tête ou au cœur.</French>
            <Spanish>Controla cuándo los jugadores pueden sufrir lesiones fatales. Una lesión fatal es causada por un daño significativo en la cabeza o el cuerpo.</Spanish>
            <Italian>Controlla quando i giocatori possono ricevere infortuni mortali. Una ferita letale è causata da un danno significativo alla testa o al torso.</Italian>
            <Polish>Definiuje, kiedy gracze mogą otrzymać śmiertelne obrażenia. Śmiertelne obrażenia są spowodowane znacznym uszkodzeniem głowy lub torsu.</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Controla quando os jogadores podem receber lesões fatais. Uma lesão fatal é causada por um dano significante na cabeça ou tronco.</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Определяет, могут ли игроки получить смертельные травмы. Смертельная травма вызывается значительным повреждением головы или туловища.</Russian>
            <German>Legt fest, wann Spieler tödliche Verletzungen erleiden können. Eine tödliche Verletzung wird bei erheblichem Schaden an Kopf oder Torso verursacht.</German>
            <Korean>플레이어가 언제 중태로 빠질 지 결정합니다. 중태는 머리나 몸통에 심각한 피해를 입는 경우 발생합니다.</Korean>
            <Japanese>プレイヤーが致命傷を受けた時の挙動を管理できます。頭部や胸部に受ける大きなダメージは致命傷になります。</Japanese>
            <Chinese>控制當玩家受致命傷時是否能救起。致命傷是指對頭部或身體造成可觀傷害所造成的。</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>控制当玩家受致命伤时是否能救起。致命伤是指对头部或躯干遭受重大伤害。</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Oyuncuların ölümcül yaralanmaları ne zaman alabileceğini kontrol eder. Ölümcül bir yaralanma, kafaya veya vücuda önemli hasar verir.</Turkish>
            <Ukrainian>Визначає, чи можуть гравці отримати смертельні травми. Смертельна травма спричиняється значним пошкодженням голови або торсу.</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Medical_Statemachine_FatalInjuriesPlayer_DisplayName">
            <English>Player Fatal Injuries</English>
            <Czech>Smrtelná zranění hráčů</Czech>
            <French>Décès si blessure mortelle (joueurs)</French>
            <Spanish>Heridas mortales del jugador</Spanish>
            <Italian>Ferite letali su giocatori</Italian>
            <Polish>Śmiertelne Obrażenia Gracza</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Lesões Fatais do Jogador</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Смертельные травмы игрока</Russian>
            <German>Tödliche Spielerverletzungen</German>
            <Korean>플레이어 중태</Korean>
            <Japanese>プレイヤーの致命傷</Japanese>
            <Chinese>玩家致命傷</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>玩家致命伤</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Oyuncu Ölümcül Yaralanmaları</Turkish>
            <Ukrainian>Смертельні травми гравця</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Medical_Statemachine_InCardiacArrest">
            <English>In Cardiac Arrest</English>
            <Czech>V srdeční zástavě</Czech>
            <French>Provoquer un arrêt cardiaque</French>
            <Spanish>En parada cardíaca</Spanish>
            <Italian>In arresto cardiaco</Italian>
            <Polish>Zatrzymanie Akcji Serca</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Em Parada Cardíaca</Portuguese>
            <Russian>При остановке сердца</Russian>
            <German>Herzstillstand</German>
            <Korean>심정지 중</Korean>
            <Japanese>心停止中</Japanese>
            <Chinese>心搏停止中</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>心脏骤停中</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Kalbi Durdu</Turkish>
            <Ukrainian>При зупинці серця</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Medical_Statemachine_SubCategory">
            <English>States</English>
            <Czech>Stavy</Czech>
            <French>États</French>
            <Spanish>Estados</Spanish>
            <Italian>Stato</Italian>
            <Polish>Stany</Polish>
            <Portuguese>Estados</Portuguese>
            <Russian>Состояния</Russian>
            <German>Zustände</German>
            <Korean>현재 상태</Korean>
            <Japanese>状態</Japanese>
            <Chinese>狀態</Chinese>
            <Chinesesimp>状态</Chinesesimp>
            <Turkish>Devletler</Turkish>
            <Ukrainian>Стани</Ukrainian>
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>
