<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="ACE">
    <Package name="VehicleLock">
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Vehicle_Action_UnLock">
            <English>Unlock Vehicle</English>
            <German>Fahrzeug aufschließen</German>
            <Spanish>Abrir vehículo</Spanish>
            <French>Déverrouiller le véhicule</French>
            <Polish>Odblokuj pojazd</Polish>
            <Czech>Odemknout vozidlo</Czech>
            <Hungarian>Jármű nyitása</Hungarian>
            <Russian>Открыть машину</Russian>
            <Italian>Sblocca il veicolo</Italian>
            <Portuguese>Destravar veículo</Portuguese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Vehicle_Action_Lock">
            <English>Lock Vehicle</English>
            <German>Fahrzeug abschließen</German>
            <Spanish>Cerrar vehículo</Spanish>
            <French>Verrouiller le véhicule</French>
            <Polish>Zablokuj pojazd</Polish>
            <Czech>Zamknout vozidlo</Czech>
            <Hungarian>Jármű zárása</Hungarian>
            <Russian>Закрыть машину</Russian>
            <Italian>Chiudi il veicolo a chiave</Italian>
            <Portuguese>Travar Veículo</Portuguese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Vehicle_Action_Lockpick">
            <English>Lockpick Vehicle</English>
            <German>Fahrzeug knacken</German>
            <Spanish>Forzar vehículo</Spanish>
            <French>Crocheter le véhicule</French>
            <Polish>Otwórz zamek</Polish>
            <Czech>Vypáčit vozidlo</Czech>
            <Hungarian>Jármű feltörése</Hungarian>
            <Russian>Взломать замок</Russian>
            <Italian>Scassina veicolo</Italian>
            <Portuguese>Usar mixa no Veículo</Portuguese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Vehicle_Action_LockpickInUse">
            <English>Picking Lock....</English>
            <German>Schloss knacken...</German>
            <Spanish>Forzando cerradura...</Spanish>
            <French>Crochetage...</French>
            <Polish>Otwieranie zamka...</Polish>
            <Czech>Páčim vozidlo...</Czech>
            <Hungarian>Zár feltörése...</Hungarian>
            <Russian>Взламываем замок...</Russian>
            <Italian>Scassino il veicolo....</Italian>
            <Portuguese>Usando Mixa...</Portuguese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Vehicle_Item_Custom_Description">
            <English>A custom key that will open a specific vehicle.</English>
            <German>Ein Schlüssel der ein bestimmtes Fahrzeug aufschließt.</German>
            <Spanish>Una llave concreta abrirá un vehículo concreto.</Spanish>
            <French>Une clé propre à un seul véhicule.</French>
            <Polish>Unikatowy klucz, który otworzy konkretny pojazd.</Polish>
            <Czech>Vlastní klíč, který otevře konkrétní vozidlo.</Czech>
            <Hungarian>Egy egyedi kulcs, ami egy meghatározott járművet nyit ki.</Hungarian>
            <Russian>Ключ от конкретной машины.</Russian>
            <Italian>Una chiave personalizzata che apre determinati veicoli.</Italian>
            <Portuguese>Uma chave específica que abre um veículo específico.</Portuguese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Vehicle_Item_Master_Description">
            <English>A Master Key will open any lock, no matter what!</English>
            <German>Ein Generalschlüssel der jedes Schloss öffnet...</German>
            <Spanish>Una llave maestra abrirá cualquier cierre, no importa cual!</Spanish>
            <French>Un passe-partout qui ouvrira n'importe quelle serrure.</French>
            <Polish>Uniwersalny klucz, który otworzy każdy zamek.</Polish>
            <Czech>Hlavní klíč otevře libovolný zámek, bez vyjímek!</Czech>
            <Hungarian>Egy főkulcs, ami minden zárat kinyit, helyzettől függetlenül!</Hungarian>
            <Russian>Универсальный ключ, открывающий любой замок.</Russian>
            <Italian>Un passe-partout che apre qualsiasi serratura!</Italian>
            <Portuguese>Uma chave mestre irá abrir qualquer fechadura, não importa qual!</Portuguese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Vehicle_Item_Lockpick_Description">
            <English>A lockpick set that can pick the locks of most vehicles.</English>
            <German>Ein Dietrich der die meisten Fahrzeugschlösser knacken kann...</German>
            <Spanish>Un set de ganzúas que puede abrir las cerraduras de la mayoría vehículos.</Spanish>
            <French>Un crochet qui ouvrira la plupart des véhicules.</French>
            <Polish>Zestaw wytrychów, dzięki któremu można otworzyć zamki w większości pojazdów.</Polish>
            <Czech>Sada paklíčů, která dokáže odemknout zámky u většiny vozidel.</Czech>
            <Hungarian>Egy tolvajkulcs-készlet, mely a legtöbb jármű zárjait fel tudja törni.</Hungarian>
            <Russian>Набор отмычек, которым можно взломать почти любую машину.</Russian>
            <Italian>Un grimardello per forzare la maggior parte dei veicoli</Italian>
            <Portuguese>Um set de chave mixas que pode abrir a maioria dos veículos.</Portuguese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Vehicle_Item_West_Description">
            <English>A key that should open most WEST vehicles.</English>
            <German>Ein Schlüssel der die meisten westlichen Fahrzeuge öffnen sollte...</German>
            <Spanish>Una llave que abrirá la mayoría de vehículos occidentales.</Spanish>
            <French>Une clé qui ouvrira la plupart des véhicules OUEST.</French>
            <Polish>Klucz, który powinien otworzyć większość pojazdów ZACHODU.</Polish>
            <Czech>Klíč který by měl otevřít většinou Západních vozidel.</Czech>
            <Hungarian>Egy kulcs, ami a NYUGAT egységeinek legtöbb járművét ki tudja nyitni.</Hungarian>
            <Russian>Ключ для открытия большинства машин Красных.</Russian>
            <Italian>Una chiave che apre la maggior parte dei veicoli occidentali</Italian>
            <Portuguese>Uma chave que abre a maioria dos veículos ocidentais</Portuguese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Vehicle_Item_East_Description">
            <English>A key that should open most EAST vehicle.</English>
            <German>Ein Schlüssel der die meisten östlichen Fahrzeuge öffnen sollte...</German>
            <Spanish>Una llave que abrirá la mayoría de vehículos orientales.</Spanish>
            <French>Une clé qui ouvrira la plupart des véhicules EST.</French>
            <Polish>Klucz, który powinien otworzyć większość pojazdów WSCHODU.</Polish>
            <Hungarian>Egy kulcs, ami a KELET egységeinek legtöbb járművét ki tudja nyitni.</Hungarian>
            <Czech>Klíč který by měl otevřít vetšinu Východních vozidel.</Czech>
            <Russian>Ключ для открытия большинства машин Синих.</Russian>
            <Italian>Una chaive che apre la maggior parte dei veicoli orientali</Italian>
            <Portuguese>Uma chave que abre a maioria dos veículos orientais</Portuguese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Vehicle_Item_Indp_Description">
            <English>A key that should open most INDEP vehicle.</English>
            <German>Ein Schlüssel der die meisten Fahrzeuge der Aufständischen öffnen sollte...</German>
            <Spanish>Una llave que abrirá la mayoría de vehículos independientes.</Spanish>
            <French>Une clé qui ouvrira la plupart des véhicules INDEP.</French>
            <Polish>Klucz, który powinien otworzyć większość pojazdów INDFOR.</Polish>
            <Hungarian>Egy kulcs, ami a FÜGGETLEN egységek legtöbb járművét ki tudja nyitni.</Hungarian>
            <Czech>Klíč který by měl otevřít většinu Nezávislých vozidel.</Czech>
            <Russian>Ключ для открытия большинства машин Независимых.</Russian>
            <Italian>Una chaive che apre la maggior parte dei veicoli degli indipendenti</Italian>
            <Portuguese>Uma chave que abre a maioria dos veículos independentes</Portuguese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Vehicle_Item_Civ_Description">
            <English>A key that should open most CIV vehicle.</English>
            <German>Ein Schlüssel der die meisten zivilen Fahrzeuge öffnen sollte...</German>
            <Spanish>Una llave que abrirá la mayoría de vehículos civiles.</Spanish>
            <French>Une clé qui ouvrira la plupart des véhicules CIV.</French>
            <Polish>Klucz, który powinien otworzyć większość pojazdów CYWILNYCH.</Polish>
            <Czech>Klíč který by měl otevřít většinu Civilních vozidel.</Czech>
            <Hungarian>Egy kulcs, ami a CIVIL járművek többségét ki tudja nyitni.</Hungarian>
            <Russian>Ключ для открытия большинства машин Гражданских.</Russian>
            <Italian>Una chaive che apr ela maggior parte dei veicoli civili</Italian>
            <Portuguese>Uma chave que abre a maioria dos veículos civis.</Portuguese>
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>
