<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Edited with tabler. -->
<Project name="ACE">
    <Package name="Inventory">
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Inventory_SettingName">
            <English>Make Inventory Display Bigger</English>
            <German>Erhöhe die angezeigte Inventargröße</German>
            <Spanish>Hacer la pantalla de inventario mas grande</Spanish>
            <Russian>Сделать окно инвентаря больше</Russian>
            <Czech>Zvětšit zobrazení inventáře</Czech>
            <Hungarian>Legyen a felszerelés menüje nagyobb</Hungarian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_Inventory_SettingDescription">
            <English>Normally inventory display is scaled by UI size. This allows scaling the Inventory UI size up, but doesn't increase font size allowing more rows displayed.</English>
            <German>Im Regelfall wird die Inventargröße durch die Größe der Nutzeroberfläche bestimmt. Diese Einstellung erlaubt es das Inventar unter Ausschluss der Schriftgröße zu vergrößern. Dadurch können mehr Gegenstände angezeigt werden.</German>
            <Spanish>Normalmente la pantalla de inventario se escala por el tamaño de la interfaz de usuario. Esto permite ampliar el tamaño de la interfaz de usuario de inventario, pero no aumenta el tamaño de fuente, permitiendo mostrar más filas.</Spanish>
            <Russian>Обычно, окно инвентаря зависит от размеров пользовательского интерфейса. Эта настройка позволяет увеличить размер окна инвентаря в пользовательском интерфейсе, не увеличивая размера шрифтов, так что отображется большее количество строк.</Russian>
            <Czech>Normálně se velikost invetáře škáluje s velikostí UI. Toto nastavení dovoluje škálování velikost inventáře ale nežvětšuje velikost fontu. To dovoluje zobrazení více řad v inventáři.</Czech>
            <Hungarian>Alaphelyzetben a kezelőfelület mérete skálázza a felszerelési menüt. Ez az opció engedélyezi a menü felskálázását, de megtartja a betűméreteket, így növelve a láthatóságot.</Hungarian>
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>